This is how it always begins.
That one's yours?
Yes. Our first.
Lucky!
I can't get off the ferry
without tripping over another one.
Well, I should get back to Yui.
Looks like we got a couple more
P.L. kids on our hands, huh?
We're over in, uh, Cranberry, where're you guys?
And one for you.
Aw, thank you, Min-Gi.
Are you sure you don't want
your viola instead of that toy?
It's a proper instrument.
Min-Gi!
Did everybody get one?
Mm-hmm!
Stop touching me!
Ugh. Can we get this
over with already?
Ready?
Heh-heh!
Ah!
Five, six, eleven, twelve!
I'm gonna dress my cat in a toque!
I'm gonna dress my dog in a toque!
Hey, get off of me!
Go away!
I'm gonna dress my cat in a toque!
I'm gonna dress my dog in a toque!
I'm gonna dress my dog in a toque...
I'm gonna dress my cat in a toque!
And after we're famous in Canada,
which'll probably only take
a few months, probably,
we'll take my dad's van
across the border,
Your dad'll never let you drive it!
He will.
And then we'll become
rockstars and play...
New York City!
Our lives are gonna be great!
Oh yeah.
That is...
if the world isn't destroyed by The Worm first!
Oh, I almost forgot!
You ready for Battle?
Wh-What? Maybe? Why?
Uh... says you have to
be in grade 12.
Whaaat?
We could just lie.
No!
Okay, so yeah...
They're not ready for
Nevsky and the Prospekts anyway.
Wait, I thought we were gonna
call ourselves Chicken Choice Judy.
It's just not a proper band name.
Min-Gi!
Your viola teacher is here.
Ryan, it's time to leave.
I packed you some oranges.
Oh, I don't need any oranges.
Thank you.
Aigoooo, you should eat oranges.
They are very healthy for you!
Here, fresh oranges.
They're very good for you!
Uhhhh...
Where've you been, man?
We're almost on!
Sorry. I was...
I...
have something for you.
Amazing.
Another round of applause
for Puppy Academy!
Oh, dude!
My dad said
we could have the van,
so after we graduate,
we're goin' on the road!
Wait, when?
Next week!
We still have a week to pack!
To pack my whole life?!
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm telling you right now.
This was always the plan!
B-B-But...
Coming up next, it's...
a... band without a name?
Chicken Choice Judy!
Uh, okay.
You ready, Min?
Min?
Hey, you're up!
Where's your buddy?
I...
don't know.
Some people say
A smile is just
an upside-down frown
But me, I know the truth
I asked for eggs over hard!
These are medium at best.
Sorry.
I'll get you a new plate.
We're goin' straight to the top
Yeah, we're gonna
live on the sun
Woo, we're goin'
straight to the top
And we're gonna have fun
Isn't it time
to put that away?
How are your university
applications going, honey?
Hey guys, I'm Ryan,
but for the next 15 minutes,
you'll be hearing
the sick licks of Gage.
What's got four wheels
and a groovy sputter?
My dad's van, my dad's van
What's got peeling paint
and a photo of my mother?
My dad's van, my dad's van
Windows rolled down,
steering wheel's hot
My dad's van is everything
you're not
I'm sorry.
Congratulations, Min-Gi.
Good job!
It's over, Ryan!
Ugh!
Wow, thanks for the van.
But I'm still
breaking up with you.
Fella over there
didn't finish his browns,
so I'm takin' 'em.
Night, Min-Gee.
It's Gi!
Hard G.
Ryan?
Just, uh... gimme a sec?
Gotta close out.
Oh yeah, take your time.
Wow, shift manager.
Even got a framed photo
and everything.
Oops.
You think that's gnarly?
Check these out.
Keys to the Dumpty Kingdom.
Yeah, I thought writing lyrics
was gonna be hard,
but it's super easy!
Just gotta make it rhyme.
When your parents said
you'd be here,
I kinda thought you'd be eating.
Not working.
Well, I mean, I also eat here.
so you were sorta right?
So, how are your...
I've got a show in New York!
Like, a real life, actual show in a couple days,
just like we talked about
in this booth back in middle school.
It was... that booth.
Are you sure it was that one?
Yep. That booth.
Okay, well... I'm going tonight, and...
I think you should come with.
Chicken Choice Judy rides again!
We can do it, together, and...
Ryan, I can't.
But music's what we always wanted!
It's what you always wanted.
I got into uni.
I'm gonna major in finance,
with an emphasis on risk assessment.
Oh. You excited?
Ryan, I'm sorry.
But I can't just leave on a whim.
C'mon, Ryan.
Ryan?
Ryan!
This isn't funny!
I have to lock up!
If you won't follow your dreams,
then I'll make ya!
Follow your dreams
somewhere people aren't sleeping!
Ryan, no!
Ryan!
Uh, 'scuse me, sorry.
Uh, I just—I just gotta get over to him.
He has my keys.
Mm-mm.
Ryan!
Two in one?
What is this, some sort of destiny rubbish?
No. It is mathematics, Amelia.
My algorithms are designed
to account for a statistical probability
that anything can happen
on the train.
Anything?
It depends, of course.
But even if the odds
are highly improbable,
given enough time, yes.
Anything.
But once these two arrive
at their seat,
it is up to them
to sort things out.
And if they don't?
Then they die here.