Huh? Hmm!
Huh?
Aaaaaaah!
Aaah!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Oh, whoa.
It is, like, way too early
for all this yelling.
Aaaaah! It's talking!
Aaaaah! Where are we?
What are you?!
What were you doing to us?
Come near us again
and I'll throw my...
I'll throw my...
giant metal boot at you?
These aren't mine.
Where are my runners?
Pretty rad boots, though.
Uh, yeah.
Uh, those don't come off.
Not rad!
What are we wearing?
Where's my guitar?
Aah!
What is this?!
I have it, too!
Did you do this?
Ugh. No!
I thought you were, like, dead.
I was trying to see
if your breath would, like,
fog up my face or whatever.
I'm Kez.
I'm Min-Gi.
This is Ryan.
The last thing I remember
is getting on a train
and then getting on...
a... second... train?
Yes!
And then a bright light!
And now waking up here!
Where are we?
Wow.
So, you're, like,
brand-brand-new.
Cool.
I've never done the whole, like,
explanation thing before.
Okay. Okay, so,
you know how in life,
you make, like, choices?
I guess.
But there were other choices
you could have made, too?
And that woulda been, like,
different?
Uh... sure.
So, it's basically that.
What?
Is this why you don't usually
do the explanation?
Okay, so, like,
where are you from?
Powell Lake.
Both of you?
Huh. Okay.
Well, anyway,
you're not in Powell Lake.
Canada?
No! This isn't
Powell Lake Canada.
America?
Guys, guys, no!
This isn't Powell Lake
Canada America.
Why does your house
have such a long name?
That's not the name
of our house.
Apartment, whatever.
Okay.
So, it's like...
Okay, so, you're in, like,
a secret pocket
that opened up in your world,
and you, like, climbed inside
and it's, like, in the pocket.
"Whoa! Here are some keys!
Here's some lint!
And here's, like,
an iceberg or whatever."
How?
I dunno!
What am I, a pocket scientist?!
Oh, right.
Okay, we just met.
So, like, for the record,
I'm not a pocket scientist.
Get back here, Kez!
You won't get away that easy!
Oh, right.
I was being chased.
You forgot you were
being chased?!
Well, I got distracted
by you two corpses.
We're gonna make a raft,
and when we're done with you,
you'll be nothing but particles!
Your little passenger
friends, too!
Oooooh, you guys are in trouble.
We're all in trouble!
Right. Okay.
So, they're, like, probably mad
the car
isn't, like, warm anymore.
This was a warm iceberg?
Nah, man,
that's a different car.
Come here.
So, this thing that was next
to the exit door...
I thought it was
a vending machine.
Tsk. I wanted some gum.
You can chew gum?
I guess I'll never know now,
will I?
Uh, how does it work?
I dunno.
I tried to use it,
and it just got,
like, super cold.
Like, everywhere.
And then those fish were,
like, pretty mad.
Ah! Whoa, dude!
This is crazy!
How do we even get home?
I'm supposed to start uni
in September.
Wow. Huge tragedy.
What?
Nothing.
Nothing!
Fine.
What?!
Whatever. Let's just figure
this thermostat out
before those Parka Fish
get here.
Aaah! Too warm!
Cool.
Aah!
Dang.
Let me try.
What, like you'll know how
to use a magic thermostat
better than me?
Huh?
What?!
What are you doing?!
Ryan!
This isn't a thermostat!
It's an era... stat
or something.
It's changing
the geological eras!
Like we're watching them
go through evolution!
What are you, a dial scientist?
Oh, dang!
This whole time,
I thought you guys
knew each other.
We do.
But he doesn't know
what you do for a living?
Kinda weird!
Aaah!
Aah!
Uhh...
Hah!
Aah!
Wha?
Aaah!
Oh, you think it's funny
to scramble our DNA?!
This will be nothing
compared to what you will suffer
when we catch you!
Your atoms will go nuclear!
Your cells will implode!
Okay, you're right.
It's an era-stat!
Gimme!
Hey!
Ah, too far in the future!
You're the one
who changed it this time!
I wasn't accusing you!
I was just saying!
We are the One True Thought.
We know all.
You have angered
the One True Thought
and must be eliminated.
Whoa. They know all.
Hey, One True Thought,
can I chew gum?
Yes.
Oh!
What flavor should I try first?
Grape.
Oh. Um...
You know what? I'm good.
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
What do we do?!
We've tried everything!
Too far left, and they're rocks!
Too far right, and they're eyes!
G-Give it to me!
Stop acting like you know
more than me!
Stop acting like a child!
Huh?
Oh, yeah!
This is what it looked
like before!
The dial thingy was in that.
The blue went into the past,
and the red
went into the future.
Heh.
You three are unbelievable!
We fixed it!
We didn't know,
and, in Kez's defense,
it does look
like a vending machine.
If you didn't start
in the Ice Age,
why have you been wearing
parkas this whole time?
We were about to leave
for a ski trip,
not that it's
any of your business!
We've got a different trip
in mind now, though.
One where we come over there,
re-program the Eon Oscillator
to control your evolution,
and send you back
to the darkness of time!
Okay, door, door, door, door!
Alright, Kez!
Come here Kez!
Uh, so, sorry about
this and all,
but, like, can't have you
chasing us, so...
Kez! No!
Oh, come on!
Wow. That was...
I mean, man.
Right?
What?
We're still on a train?!
Uh, yeah. Remember?
I explained that.
No! You just said
we're "in a pocket"!
That was it!
"In a pocket."
Oh.
Well, you're in a pocket,
and you got here by, like,
getting on the train.
And you have to learn lessons
and stuff,
and get your number
down to zero.
Otherwise, the train
won't let you off.
Lessons?
Yeah, 'cause you were, like,
screwing up your lives and junk.
Never heard of two people
getting on
at the same time, though.
That's wild.
Same number, too.
Wild.
You bought the tickets.
Dude, for the normal train!
I didn't go to the metro station
and say, "Hi! Two tickets
on the Wormhole Judgment Line."
Well, I definitely didn't have
anything to do with this.
I was having a totally normal
night at Dumpty's when...
You working at a
Humpty Dumpty-themed restaurant
is anything but normal.
Wow. And you guys
are mortal enemies, too?
What are the odds?
What?!
We're not enemies.
Ryan is my best friend.
Yeah.
Could two enemies have figured
out that dial thing together?
Well, I mean, yeah,
'cause you didn't figure it out
so much as, like, fight over it
until it randomly fell
into place.
We weren't fighting.
Yeah. We were just...
I don't know.
We were just talking.
Totally.
It's just that...
you don't really know us.
Yeah. We're fine.
We're great.
Okay. You know what?
Let's not stress
about dials or trains
or numbers or anything.
Let me just take you back
to my place, and we can chill.
Cool, cool.
You'll meet my roommate, Morgan.
It'll be great. Good.
This is good!
Cause', like honestly,
in my opinion,
sometimes numbers
are a part of the problem,
not the solution, you know?
Yeah, you get it.
Okay, come on.
How far is your place, anyway?
Eh, just a couple
dozen cars back.
Does that mean
there are more cars
with more people out to get us?
Ah, nah!
Most people are super chill.
Aah!
Well, if it ain't our ol' friend
Cactus Kez.