Cactus Kez.
You got a lotta nerve showin'
your face around these parts.
More friends of yours?
Pffft! These squares?
I don't think so.
There's a whole mess of people
that just can't wait
to get their prolegs
on the likes of you.
Looks like she got a couple
of new goons with her, too.
Hold on!
We just met her!
Get ready to be, like, dazzled!
What do you... Aah!
Run!
My multi-lensed eyes!
Come on!
Hey! It burns!
A warning would have been nice!
Huh? I totally gave you one.
Draw!
Hey! Any of y'all seen
two varmints and an outlaw?
Where'd they go?
Saloon!
They go this way
or they go that way?
Anybody seen 'em around here?
Uh, maybe she can help?
Man's best friend.
What?
Yeah, hey. Could I get, like,
three cups of hot tea?
Wait.
I got these, like... last week.
They're still good, right?
You didn't pay for them
last week.
We're being chased.
Aren't we all?
We need a place to hide.
And what's in it for me?
Uh... uh...
For someone so beautiful?
I'm sure we can
arrange... something.
Hmm?
I respect the moxie,
but I've already got plenty.
Ugh! Why can't anything
just be easy?
When did your numbers sync?
Sync? They've been this way
since we got on.
At the same time?
A buy-one-get-one-free
passenger?
That's a curiosity worth saving.
Uh... heh. Ooh!
Ma'am.
Thirsty, Sheriff?
We're lookin' for an outlaw.
Small. Silver.
She's got a vacant stare that
goes on for miles and miles.
Like this.
With a pair of needy
little passengers.
I appreciate the clarification.
But I'm afraid I haven't
seen anyone
matching that description...
'round these parts.
Je m'excuse.
Alright, then.
We'll be on our way.
Let's go, boys!
But if you do see Kez,
I have it on good authority
that Judge Morpho
has a big bounty out on her.
Bounty?
Why did you flirt with a cat?
I dunno, man.
She was kinda hot.
I got us a hiding place,
didn't I?
With someone who immediately
sold us out!
I didn't hear you coming up
with a plan.
Yeah, so I'm kinda done
with all this.
Get ready for, like, the drop.
Kez, you could have
woken up the guard!
I, like, gave you a heads up.
You shoulda said something.
Oh, yeah! My stuff!
Is that a photo?
Yeah. This is Morgan.
Cute, right?
That should be everything.
Nice.
So, what do we do next?
Oh, yeah. Uh, you two.
Um, well...
I'll do my half, and, I mean,
you two can, like,
keep an eye out for me,
and, uh, I'll have your back.
Oof.
Rude.
There is absolutely no way
he's coming back for us.
What do we do now?
Keys might be a start.
So...
do you think our parents
know where we are?
In an Old West bug jail?
I'm gonna say no.
But they'll wonder
where we went to.
At least...
yours probably will.
Yeah.
Yes! Ha ha!
Hmph!
What do you two think you're...
What have you done?!
We didn't do anything!
Well, here.
Pretty clear.
I-I can see it.
Right.
We did do that.
But we have nothing
to do with Kez.
We don't even understand
half the stuff she says.
Save it for the judge.
Hush up!
I said, "Hush up,"
the lot of you.
Show some gosh dang respect
for the honorable
and migratory Judge Morpho.
It's a judge.
They gotta be fair.
What the... What the...
What is that?
Eww. Is the hat part
of her skin?
How does that work?
Ugh.
Order! Order!
That means shut
your dang mandibles!
That's better.
Now, sounds like I got a fair
and impartial trial
to preside over.
As you always do, Your Honor.
These two ruffians here
are part of
Cactus Kez's new gang.
Any witnesses to that?
Yes, Your Honor... you...
in your larval state.
Mm-hmm.
That checks out.
And they broke Cactus Kez outta
jail to commit more crimes.
Hey, Min, I have an idea.
Maybe not the best time.
Hey Judge!
I mean, Your Honor.
I'd like to approach the bench.
Would you, now?
I'm a simple man.
A simple family man.
Min-Gi's even simpler.
When we came
into your town, we...
Guilty!
What?!
No way!
Perfect as always, Your Honor.
Swift and mighty justice!
Whoo-hoo!
How can we be guilty?
We don't even know
what we're charged with.
Our town used to be
a little slice of heaven.
Beetle Bailiff?
Our way of life was preserved
in that there charter.
But Cactus Kez's understanding
of the law
is as loose as her
understanding of coasters.
You can't lock us up
for a tea stain!
I'd like to sentence
you two fairly,
but that part of our charter
ain't legible no more.
Using my personal
and unbiased discretion,
I sentence you two
to the zapper,
where you will fry, fry, fry!
Zap! Zap! Zap! Zap!
Zap! Zap! Zap! Zap! Zap!
Hope y'all are ready
to be dazzled
by 2,000 volts of justice!
Dazzled.
We kept not understanding Kez.
The flash, the cage.
She bailed on us, Min.
She said
she'd "have our backs."
Think.
But think like Kez would.
Cactus Kez is back!
She's got the town charter!
And she's fixin'
to finish the job!
Git 'er!
Kez.
Settle down!
Let's get through one set
of executions at a time!
Uh... uh... ugh!
Aaaaah!
Hey! Aah!
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Hey, guys! Great job
with your half of the plan.
If you're here,
then who's back there?
It's that foxy stunt double
from the saloon. Mmm!
You set all that up
to distract them and save us?
Yeah.
That's what I said.
A bounty for turning you in
and a favor for helping you out.
An excellent plan,
if I do say so myself.
It's fake!
And if you want to live
long enough to pay me back,
I suggest you get moving.
Right. Moving along now!
So...
we almost got killed.
Are we really gonna stick
with Kez?
It was a misunderstanding.
It's not her fault
we don't speak like Kez.
Heh.
Nobody speaks like Kez.
You got that right.
Hey,
what are we whispering about?
Nothing.
We're all good.
Lead the way, friendo.
Awww, you guys.
Morgan is gonna, like,
love you two.
Such little charmers!
I'm gonna find that no-good...
I'm looking for
a little silver bell.
You seen her?