I vote we keep them on.
They're stylish, man.
Yours has cool doodles.
Mine is apparently
an old person's grocery list.
Fiber powder.
Bunion pads.
Mrs. Tinsley's
Old Fashioned Butter Lozanges
for Well Behaved Boys.
No, thanks.
Aw.
Hey like, wouldn't it be fun
if I, like,
wore this hat
for the rest of the time
we were here and you, like,
called me Lorraine?
- Why?
- I don't know.
Why do you hate fun, Min?
I don't hate fun.
I just...
Oh.
Who in this car hates you?
Again, Kez?
Lorraine.
Fine.
Lorraine,
what did you do this time?
Lorraine answers to no man.
Treats for Pig Baby!
Have you brought
something tasty for Pig Baby?
Uh, I'm sorry, we didn't know
we should bring food.
We were just looking
for the door.
No treats?
You've upset Pig Baby.
Oh, aww.
Shh-shh-shh-shh-shh.
Oh, shoosh.
There, there.
Who's a pretty baby, oh?
- I am.
- That's right.
And what do pretty pigs say, ah?
Oink, oink, oink.
Aww, that's our good boy.
You must make Pig Baby
a treat to make it up to him.
Huh?
Uh, look,
Mrs. Cow Creamer,
we don't want
to upset your, uh, son?
But we have to be on our way.
Yeah, man.
We're supposed to meet up
with my roommate.
Who's that you're with?
Uh, just me.
Lorraine.
Kiss me, I'm a chef's hat.
No, thank you.
Aah!
Whoa there, Lorraine.
Dudes, just make the treat,
and we'll look
for the door later.
We can't have Pig Baby
knowing I'm here.
Okay, Mrs. Cow Creamer.
We'll make something.
Ooh, magnifique.
You'll find our kitchen
fully stocked.
Though I'm sorry
there's not more butter.
There was a bit of an incident.
Butter!
Waaaah! My butter!
Oh, there, there, plumpkins.
The cookbook is up there.
Choose wisely.
My little angel is very hard
to impress.
How are we supposed
to get up there?
You just got to jump, man.
No way, Lorraine.
Ryan, you can't just... ugh!
You have to think
before you do things.
Lorraine said to jump,
and now I'm up here
by the cookbook
and you're down there
like a chump without a cookbook.
Chicken liver anchovy toast?
Wax beans O'Brian?
Tomato frost?
Ugh, it's American.
Well, there's got to be asimple
brownie recipe or something.
Min, please.
The Creamer said
to wow Pig Baby.
Here.
This one actually sounds
pretty good.
It also looks
pretty complicated.
We'll be fine.
Go big or go home.
If we can ever even get home.
And the final touch.
If I was at Dumpty's right now,
I would be ashamed
to serve this.
Puh-lease.
It had tons of ingredients,
so like, um, you know,
confidence.
Didn't puree the strawberries,
over-whipped the egg whites,
and you chose chiffon
even though it needs
to be chilled overnight.
But we took a pretty big swing,
so points for that at least?
We'll do better.
It's fine.
We'll find something.
Ew. Warm banana
mayonnaise salad?
Ugh, Americans, man.
Great music, disgusting
post-war food.
I say we try it.
He's a pig, right?
He probably loves
gross American food.
Why else would this be
the only cookbook?
Aww.
You forgot the lettuce,
and it's cold.
Custard does not
have beef floss.
Zippers are not a food.
You got to respect someone
trying to innovate
in their field.
No, Lorraine, I don't.
Try again, and perhaps
try finding something simple
that actually tastes good
from that disgusting cookbook,
which was the only one left
after a tragic grease fire.
Pig Baby doesn't like that food?
Who in their right mind
enjoys post-war American food?
- I told you.
- I know. Okay?
I know. Whatever.
We'll do brownies.
Fine.
Well, this will come
as a surprise to no one.
We're out of butter.
Aw, man. My butter.
I hope it's okay.
Kez?
Were you the butter incident?
So, like,
maybe when I was here last time,
I put a bunch of butter
in the microwave,
set it for five minutes, forgot,
and, like,
maybe all the butter melted.
- And then you what, left?
- Or what?
Stay in the kitchen forever?
I am not about to turn the clock
back on women's lib, man.
Kez!
Ugh.
It'll be fine.
Follow me.
I mean, at the end of the day,
it's still butter, right?
Aah!
Wait.
Okay, they're done.
Shouldn't
the toothpick be clean?
Nah, that would mean
they're too dry.
They need to be kind of fudgy
in the middle.
Because otherwise
it'd just be cake.
Look who's suddenly
a brownie expert.
It was in the recipe book.
Ooh-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo,
a humble brownie expert.
Well, what can I say?
"Your Honor,
I am a simple man."
Okay, okay.
"A simple brownie man."
Huh?
Oh, your numbers went down.
Um, cool.
You learned to slow down.
What?
We're here
to learn lessons, right?
That's the thing
that just happened.
You took your time
with something for once, and...
Hey.
And if you're the one
who learned something,
then that means...
I'm the one
who made the numbers change.
Yes.
So you're the one who was meant
to be on the train, not me.
Oh.
I didn't know.
I wouldn't have made you
follow me if...
Ah, I forgive you.
It was a freak accident,
and I'll do everything I can
to help you mature.
Huh. Maybe the lesson
didn't stick.
Maybe you need to prove
you learned it
by doing it again in the future.
I guess?
Ready to give a treat
to a fussy baby?
Sure, man.
Yummers!
Ooh, excellent work.
I've never seen Pig Baby
so delighted by a treat.
More.
Mais oui.
What? No.
He's happy now,
so we're gonna exit.
No, no.
You will keep cooking.
Pig Baby must be kept happy.
Until Pig Baby dies,
and you'll be the new Pig Baby.
No way, you creepy creamer.
Pig Baby ate the exit.
We have to find a way in there.
This car is messed, man.
How are we supposed to get him
to stop chewing?
Butter Kez.
Kez melted all
of Pig Baby's yummy butter.
Okay, Pig Baby, like,
we're all just adults here,
so let's just...
Waaaahhhhh!
Come now.
Oh, be a brave.
Oh, would you like some lard?
Does a sweet widdle baby
want some lard?
Waaaahhhhh!
Aw, gross, man.
Here's hoping we don't
have to cook again
to get your number down.
Yeah. Right.
Right, right, numbers.
But like we just learned,
don't push yourself, man.
Because it's not about
the desti-something.
It's about the whatever.
Yeah. You can't help it
if you have a lot to learn.