When I look at you,
I see me
And when I look at me,
I see you
It may sound kinda funny at first, but you’ll see
If you give it a try, you’ll like it, too
I’m from the West
And you’re from the East
You like to rhyme
And I don’t know how
We’re not the same, and that’s a good thing
There’s a whole lot of good bein’ different can bring
Life’s too short to only look for difference
We should learn to celebrate our difference
Aha!
I’m blue!
I’m brown!
I smile!
I frown!
I eat things backwards and upside-down!
I’ve got legs!
I’ve got none!
Where I’m from, vacuuming’s fun!
Here!
There!
Everywhere!
Who are you?
I don’t care!
Just be kind and understand
We all hail from equal lands!
Everybody!
When I look at you, I see me
When I look at me, I see you
It may sound kinda funny at first, but you’ll see
If you give it a try...
When ya give it a try...
Won’t you give it a try?
You’ll like it
too!
Take what you want, Apex!
Highest number gets
the pick of the raid!
You see that, Grace?
Already up 14!
Not bad, Simon!
Not bad?
Think you can beat it?
Already have, socks and sandals.
Ahh!
Oh, come on. Gimme a new nickname!
I was ten. My mom thought
they were practical.
Ha!
Never trust an adult!
She ever heard of “shoes”?
Ahh!
Why, no!
What are these “shoès” you speak of?
Wow. Nice combo.
Guess you win again...
kneepads.
You’re just jealous I know how
to make practical look good.
No
!
What
Help!
No
What
are
you
do
ing
Help!
Time to go?
Time to go.
It’s locked!
Ugh, another dumb train puzzle?
Barely.
Apex!
Take a bow!
When I look at you, I see me...
Lindsay! This is amazing!
This is going
in my personal stash
where only
my favorite gifts go.
Just don’t tell the others.
I wouldn’t want them
to feel bad, y’know?
Mm-hmm!
Wow, Alex!
You’re so good at presents.
Don’t tell anybody,
but I’m gonna put only these...
things... in my personal
stash of favorites.
Wow.
Please
help
!
Please
help
Oh
,
no
!
You’re
one
of
them
!
Oh
no
You’re
one
of
them
Lucy, hold that null.
Wh
-
What
What
are
you
do
ing
Shhh...
Hmm.
Mm...
Mm-mm. Nah. Too much.
One of these days, I’ll make
crushed velvet work for me.
Wheel it or whatever.
So I can keep
the light person?
No
,
no
wait!
No
no
wait!
Aw, that’s cute.
Lucy thinks it’s a person.
Simon, do you see a person?
Mm-mm.
All I see is another toy
the train made to amuse us.
See, Lucy? It’s nothing.
Just something to play with
when we’re bored.
And honestly?
You’re boring me.
Yes, Grace.
Understood, Grace!
Wait.
I want it!
Put it in my room.
Yes, Simon.
What? I’m building a diorama
for my soldiers.
I need a big light to emulate dawn
before the Battle of Esmoroth.
Is that a real battle?
It is in my fantasy novel...
Which you promised you’d read?
I’m still on the foreword!
You wrote the foreword!
I know. Isn’t it great?
Apex!
May our spirits be high!
And our numbers higher!
Down with the False Conductor!
The Apex reveals the truth!
Let’s raid another car!
I’m feeling it, yeah!
Who wants to raid one more car?
One more car!
One more car! One more car!
No sign of any passengers
in the next car.
Should be easy.
One more car!
One more car! One more car!
Ah, yeah, Chief, I’m just makin’
the ol’ desayuno for the family.
Slow-cooked lettuce
with a side of turtle juice!
Eh, it’s like regular juice,
but for turtles.
I dunno, Chief,
what’s going on?
What’s happening, Daddy?
Yeah, that’s right, now I’m reassuring
my kid Kevin Jr. not to worry
and telling him it’ll be okay.
Yuh-huh.
Well, now they’re
breaking into my home
and taking my novelty apron
and second-favorite hat!
Uh, it’s not really breaking in
when your house has no walls.
It is too breaking in!
It’s against turtle law!
Which is like regular law,
but for turtles!
No, no, no, no, no, sensei,
was yelling at a guy.
Would never dream
of yelling at you.
You’re golden, sensei. Golden!
Looks like someone wants
a new nickname, chef’s hat!
Oh, man, am I wearing one?
It’s so subtle, I hadn’t noticed.
Stop!
In the name of King Aloysius!
This car’s a shifter.
Back to the mall, Apex!
Simon!
Ahh!
Sorry, Madam Secretary,
gonna be late again.
First my breakfast is ruined,
now the whole world is flying away.
Yeah, it’s been a bad, bad, bad, bad year.
Hey.
Think I bruised a rib.
Don’t worry, I gotcha.
All right, Simon.
Hang on tight.
You sure you can carry us both?
Wanna find out?
Whoa!
Simon?
Simon!
Phew.
I owe ya one.
Dude, you owe me a million.
Also, a new raid mask.
Also, a harpoon pack.
Yours is broken?
Ugh. Beyond broken.
We’ll swap it out
back at the mall.
Can’t be that far.
What happened?
Cars aren’t supposed to move
if people are inside.
Well, you know
who can do that...
That horrible little robot.
I think the False Conductor
just made his first move.
You think he was attacking us?
I wouldn’t put it past him.
Good news!
They’re here.
Bad news, we’re...
here.
47 cars away.
Hey, that’s not all bad!
It’ll be like old times.
Just me and you.
Yeah, old times...