You okay?
This isn't going to be
a normal procedure.
You're right.
We're supposed to have backup.
We're supposed to have two
working harpoon packs.
I don't think we've even been
this far out
on the train before.
So what do we have,
besides pessimism?
Good idea.
We might have to ration.
Let's see.
We have some snack bars,
rope...
three toothbrushes?
One for the teeth,
two for the sneaks.
I don't even get one?
All I know is
I packed three.
Baggie of gorp,
Arctic Cowboy brand deodorant
for summer sports perspiration.
That's good,
because I don't need
your ripeness
giving away our position.
Aww!
You think I'm joking!
Okay. First impressions.
Looks to be
a moderately sized car,
jungle-themed...
but with a little extra...
Flair?
Hmm?
Threats seem minimal.
But Simon presence
remains aloof and dorky.
Dude, we are the Apex,
but, also, we're Grace
and Simon, remember?
Yeah.
[ Mockingly ] "Yeah."
"Yeah," what?
I've seen you lead
an army of kids,
but I've also seen you
play sock ball.
You can play super serious
general guy when we get back.
Until then,
lo-o-o-osen u-u-u-u-p!
Think of it as us
being on leave.
Whoa!
Okay.
Hmm-hmm.
See? Isn't this a nice
change of pace?
Yeah, it is.
Whoa.
Whoa!
Ohh!
Aaah!
Looks like
we got Null problems.
Can't look for
threats down here.
See anything?!
Yeah— the tops of other trees!
I think I found something!
Clear a way— now, now, now!
Whatever it is,
we can't ignore it.
I know you told me
to loosen up,
but we do have Apex procedures
for something like this.
Okay.
What do you got?
When encountering a Null
that cannot be overwhelmed
with force,
nor avoided in its entirety,
the Null in question
must be incapacitated.
Hmm. Now, who could have
written that one?
You know I don't like
to take credit for things.
Let's trap it.
Did we have marshmallows?
I'm sorry. What?
This is where you want to redeem
your loss at chubby bunny—
right here?
I maintain that I am still
the champion.
They did not fly out
until after I said it.
Still counts.
Huh?
I-It's fine.
The— The trap
let us know it's here.
Now we can team up
and take it down together.
Huh?
Simon?
Simon, where are you?!
Make some noise
so I can try to follow!
Simon!
Huh?
As punishment for being sneaky,
the trespassers are given
as food to the mighty Tuba!
Aaaaaaaaaah!
Please! Please!
Oh, stop it!
"Oh, no! Please!
Ha ha ha! Oh, no!"
That's you two!
That's what you two
sound like!
I thought you said
there weren't any passengers
for at least 47 cars.
I don't know. That's what
the number tracker said.
Uh, hi...over there.
We're with the Apex.
You might have heard of us—
seen this wave symbol?
We want to make sure
you're getting everything
you're entitled
to from the train.
Hmm.
As a passenger,
the true conductor gives us—
Pbbbbbbt!
Hmph.
Ahem.
You aren't getting this.
You see—
No!
Hmph!
You told me we don't hit!
Sorry.
He can get
a little excited.
My name's Grace.
Simon is my friend.
What's your friend's name?
This is Tuba.
She's kinda shy.
Mm. I can get shy, too.
Hi, Tuba!
Hello.
And what's your name?
Hazel.
That's a very pretty name,
I'm looking for passengers
to help.
That's what I do.
Do you mind if I talk to Hazel
alone, just for a little bit?
I should stay.
Tuba, I'll be okay.
I promise.
I will be
over here...
...eating a pineapple.
Thank you, Hazel.
Do you want to see
something cool?
This is my number.
Do you have a number?
I do!
But yours glows!
Simon, take a look at this.
That's probably why
she didn't scan.
The fake conductor was trying
to hide her from us,
turning off her number.
We need to get her
to the Apex right away.
What's a con— conductor?
Well, that's what I was trying
to tell you about before.
Let's focus on numbers.
We all have them—
me, you, and Simon.
But yours should be glowing—
like mine. See?
Hmm.
How could we fix...
Oh, I know!
You could come back with us!
That way we can teach you
all about numbers.
Maybe we can get yours
to glow like mine does!
Cool!
Plus you get to meet a bunch
of other cool kids.
Whaaaaaaaa?
Wait.
Am I kid?!
Mm-hmm.
Yes!
I'll tell Tuba to pack up.
Tuba can't come with.
What?
You can't—
What he's trying to say is
that numbers are for passengers.
This kind of stuff
doesn't affect her.
Tuba probably wants to stay
in this jungle car.
Don't be daft!
I'm not leaving Tuba.
We can't bring that Null
with us back to the Apex.
Oh, okay.
Do you think
we can just grab Hazel
and run past that thing?
Okay, Simon, listen.
We'll take them both for now.
Once we wean Hazel off it,
we'll ditch the Null
before we get back home.
Hmm.
Hazel!
I had to give Simon
a talking-to.
He was a little confused.
Of course we want both of you
to come with.
But you were the one
that said—
That was Simon,
and he was confused.
But now I fixed it.
We're all going to the Apex
together!
Isn't that exciting?
Tuba!
We're going with Grace
and that guy!
I'm gonna see more kids!
Pack up your stuff!
Are you sure this is
what you want?
We were setting up
a home here.
It's the moment
I've dreamed of my whole life.
Okay.
We got to bring the couch!
That is a rock.
Oh. We need to take the TV,
for sure.
That is also a rock.