Rookie move, buddy.
Whatever.
Battle scars
give a man character.
So when are we taking out
that null?
Well, it's big
and would put up
a serious fight.
And we could lose Hazel
if we attack it.
She's too attached.
I mean, when you first got
on the train
and that null of yours—
Uh...
[ Sighs sadly ]
Anyway...
brute force
can get so boring.
Am I right?
We've got time.
Hmm.
We made a new friend.
This is Louis.
He's a good sort,
but barking mad.
What a coincidence!
We have a friend named Louis
in the Apex.
The Apex is the country
where you're from?
The Apex isn't a place,
it's a special
secret force of kids.
Yeah, that's right!
In the Apex, we fight
for our rights as passengers
because an evil robot
named One-One
has taken over the train.
A evil robot?
Yep. See, the True Conductor
was a man
who wore big black helmet
with a red wave on it.
He has the highest number
in the world
and even saved my life once.
So we wear the red wave
on our faces to honor him.
He built the train
for humans.
But no one knows where
the True Conductor is now,
and One-One is trying to get rid
of all the humans on the train.
Ever since he took over,
kids have been disappearing
when their numbers go down.
I hate One-One!
Where do the children go?
No one knows.
But I have
the highest number,
just like
the True Conductor did,
so I'm the leader
of the Apex.
I make sure everyone's number
stays high.
Can I be in it?
Hmm.
Well, Apex kids
are all really special
and really brave.
Hmm.
Hmmmmm!
Yeah, maybe someday.
Someday.
Don't be a worry baby,
no need to hurry, baby
When you're with me
Just take it easy-peasy,
my little lemon-squeezy
'Cause you're with me
Hah!
That's cute.
Tuba used to sing it
to her kids.
But I added
the "easy-peasy" part!
Kids, huh?
So, you're probably
gonna need
to head back to 'em
at some point?
No.
I...am on my own...now.
Nuh-unh!
You're with us!
Of course.
Stop!
Stop right there!
What do you think you're doing?
Simon, get to higher ground.
I'll find its—
You aren't even dressed.
I can't present you
in such a state.
Where are your escorts?
We don't need escorts.
Where's the exit?
The exit only makes itself seen
to those who've entered society.
You must have a debut.
Procedures must be followed.
Oh. I'll take you
to the Cotillion Room
to learn the waltz.
Follow me, if you will.
What now?
We'll play along,
for Hazel's sake.
Former debutantes,
all paired off now.
Great. Look at that.
Good for them.
Well, here we are!
I'll be back to collect you
all later,
so follow the feet,
learn the steps, no mistakes,
or you'll be
trapped here forever.
Okay. Cheerio!
Hey!
You can't leave us in here!
This is what happens
when we play by train rules.
Ceiling panels might budge.
I'll take lead.
You go and—
Let's learn the dance!
Hazel! You are so sweet,
but here's the thing
about life on the train.
It is smart to try
what we know can work.
Mm.
Thank you for the input,
but—
If we don't dance,
we can't get back to the Apex!
And we have to
so I can be in it!
I can be special and brave.
I promise.
Huh?
Okay.
We'll cover our bases.
You go through the vents
and look for another way out.
I'll learn the dance.
I don't like this, Grace.
These nulls are a bigger
threat than they seemed.
They always are.
So...
let's learn this dance.
We follow the feet!
This is a ballroom dance!
Some of the steps are backwards.
We have to be partners.
You're right.
How do you know
about this stuff?
I took classes.
Do you have one of those
intense dance moms or something?
Dance moms?
Yeah.
Puts you in contests
to win trophies,
makes you wear
super tight ponytails,
gives you too much sugar?
I...
don't know.
You...don't know?
What about your dad?
He was...
Ugh! I don't know!
What does she know?
Okay. That's okay.
Hey, I had dance lessons,
too.
Yeah?
Yeah! All kinds—
tap, hip-hop, ballet.
Couples do ballroom
as a fun bonding activity.
Uh...
yeah, I guess so.
I never did ballroom,
though.
I didn't go to classes.
I had private instruction.
No other kids?
Yeah. My mom and dad were all
about "learning from the best,"
which always just meant
I was alone.
One year, my instructor put me
in her group class recital,
but my parents couldn't come,
and the other girls in the class
didn't know me,
so they didn't invite me
to get ice cream afterward.
But, really, they were
just jealous
because I was way
better than them,
which got so boring,
so I quit.
It's okay.
I don't know
any other kids, either.
Hmm.
Whoa! Ugh!
Simon!
I looked for a way
out of the building.
Grace, there's literally
nothing out there.
It's just a black void.
Okay. Let me think.
Well, the dance is our
obvious option right now.
But—
And if it doesn't
get us to the exit,
then we'll make them regret
they ever met us.
So be my partner already!
You know, we're not
half bad at this.
Must be all the drills
we run together.
Sure.
What's a little box step
when you've taken the head
off a 6-foot vulture together?
It's time, my lovelies!
I present to you as their entrée
into society
the Mighty Tuba,
Hazel Last Name Unknown,
Simon Laurent,
and Grace Monroe.
And now the couples will take
their first dance together.
What a handsome young man.
I must introduce
my nephew to her.
Is that a gorilla?
I don't know,
but she's stunning.
I think that one's
a little young.
Shh! Please!
Finally!
Whoo-hoo! We did it!
You did it, Hazel!
We would never have learned
the dance without you.
You know, Simon...
I think she's ready.
Congratulations.
You're Apex now.
I was brave?
Mm-hmm.
Now Tuba!
Oh, man.
We totally would,
but the red waves
are for kids only.
Are you a kid, Tuba?
No.
I am not a kid.
See? She's not a kid,
so we can't.
Being Apex is so fun!
Hey, why don't you teach me
that cute song
you were singing earlier?
Okay!
The first part is...
Don't be a worry baby
Mm-hmm.
No need to hurry, baby
When you're with me