Mm.
Everyone, keep your bodies
moving.
It may not be flashy,
but frostbite is just as deadly
as lava moles
or bottomless pits.
And the best way to keep
the circulation going is...
Better watch out, Hazel!
No, you watch out!
Get him, Hazel!
Take this! Ha-ha!
Ahhh!
We need backup!
He's gonna out-snow—
he's gonna hit us!
Ah, it's not holding.
You gotta warm the snow
with your hands first.
Your real hands.
Of course.
What would I do
without you?
You would die
until you're dead.
Watch this!
Huh?
Ah!
Uh...
Tuba!
We need the big one!
Huh? W-Wait!
Armistice!
Arm—
Armistice means
no more snowballs.
I know.
Ahh.
Snow's probably
gonna get worse.
What's the plan?
What?
Cabin.
Grace?
Huh?
Oh, yeah...
uh...
let's head to the cabin.
The first vacation I've taken
in 150 years,
and I have to deal
with tourists.
The Cat?
Grace.
Raiding my business
isn't enough for—
Simon?
Well, I suppose you can stay
for a bit.
We gotta go.
We just got here.
We're not staying here.
Snow day!
No.
We're leaving.
We're leaving!
Simon, the snow's too heavy,
we have to hunker down.
And stay here with her?
And figure things out.
Figure wha—
I'm gonna go look
for supplies.
Hmm?
Huh?
Whoo!
It's laughing water!
It's a laughing girl!
I am!
Randall.
You were brought here
for ambiance, not conversation.
Oh, right.
Not a peep.
You don't look like
the normal Apex riff-raff.
I'm Hazel.
This is Tuba.
Mm.
She's a tough customer.
Clearly.
Oh, my.
What happened
to your number?
Grace and Simon said
One-One turned it off.
We hate him!
Ah, bon?
One-One?
Mm-hmm.
Let's take a closer look.
If you talk to her again,
I'll...
You'll what?
You couldn't stop me
with your whole army.
What are you gonna do
with the B-squad?
Hey, I'm making pancakes.
You kids got
any allergies?
Not now, Frank.
Okay.
Huh?
You walked into my cabin.
Stay away.
Okay, Simon.
Did you find something
to...
Supplies?
Like, "we're staying here
and not leaving" supplies?
Where else
are we gonna go?
This tea has a bug
with a cowboy hat on it,
that's how you know
it's the good stuff.
Come on, Tuba.
I'll be mother.
I thought we were trying to find
a way to get out of here.
It's a blizzard out there.
So what am I supposed to—
I don't know, Simon!
Do I need to make
every decision for you?
Go...
look for something.
Uh...
Huh?
Flavor is
all about timing.
Really?
Too long or too short.
Both can ruin your tea
and day.
The best way...
I told you to stay away!
I was trying to be helpful.
I know what you think
is helpful!
Why can't I talk to her?
Because she abandoned me!
Before I met Grace,
there was the Cat.
She was there
in my first train car,
before I even knew
there were train cars.
She was my Tuba.
And after a few months
of "helping" me,
she left me
left me alone to die.
Simon...
Am I wrong?
Did you leave me or not?
You're not...
wrong...
I was 10 years old!
I was a child!
And you left me to a gohm.
If Grace didn't show up,
I wouldn't be here.
But what's with you?
Every minute I'm in this cabin
with the Cat
is like another weight
pressing down on my chest.
And you don't even seem
to care.
Wh—
She's collecting again.
I'm sorry.
This must be horrible
for you.
I should have seen it,
but...
I've been dealing with...
something.
It's been going down.
I don't know when it started,
but I can't stop it.
I didn't want the Apex,
or you...
to see me like this.
To think less of me.
I'm always with you.
We're a team.
Huh?
I'm all naturally flavored.
I got it from the tap,
I swear!
Is all the water here,
Randall?
While the view here
is magnificent,
it's been bone dry
for centuries.
The snow.
Hmm.
Aww, you got me.
It took a lot of effort
to import that much Randall.
You don't find paradise,
you make it.
We need to get
out of here.
Can you stop
the blizzard?
Blizzard?
Oh, you mean
the snowball fight?
We saw you all having fun
and wanted to join in.
Well, we called an...
armistice?
Yeah.
So you gotta stop it, okay?
Oh, sounds good to me.
But Randall is about
a mile in the air.
I've got an idea.
Oh, and I'd have to talk
to Randall and Randall.
And of course Randall
would need to give
his approval for
all of this.
You don't boil friends!
Actually, I kind of like it.
I don't judge.
Bring it in, guys!
Snowball fight's over.
Did we win?
Armistice.
Now we get
to the fun part—
negotiation of terms.
Oh, it's best
when both sides
can feel like the winner,
isn't it?
Inspired thought, Randall.
I'll be giving that one a lot
of reflection.
Boop.
Au revoir, Simon.
Au revoir.