My legs are tired!
Yeah,
let's all take a nap
on a rusty outdoor bridge
when we're almost home.
Okay.
No, Hazel, get up.
Hazel is tired.
It is nap time.
Move...
before
I make you move.
Okay!
Hey, hey, hey!
Simon is right.
We are too close to The Apex
to slow down now.
But Tuba's got a point.
We've been going hard for days,
and Hazel's just a little girl.
So we'll do both.
Tuba, you carry Hazel
while she naps.
But we press on.
No stopping.
All right?
The null's more hindrance
than help.
Let's get
rid of her now.
No.
She's too strong.
We'll have the rest of The Apex
to help soon enough.
Bet ya I can take her solo.
No, Simon.
Is that a dare?
No.
It's Red O'Clock!
[ Ticking ]
Welcome,
friends and future friends,
to the Color Clock!
You can call me Roy,
'cause I'm your boy!
I've got this.
That sounds fun, Roy.
What's the deal
with the exit?
Oh, I can't
tell you.
See, it's my job to
keep the way out a secret.
You'll have to use teamwork
if you want to solve the puzzle!
Ah!
Oops, I've said too much!
Ugh, we got
another key car.
It's Orange O'Clock!
Hello, and welcome to
the Color Clock!
You can call me Roy,
'cause—
You are our boy.
Huh. Guess word
gets around fast.
Wowee! Wow! Wow!
A team of four?!
We're not a team.
Word to the wise?
Teamwork begins with
two people trusting each other.
Oh! Spoiler!
Ah! I've said too much!
Hee-hee-hee-hee-hee!
All right.
Looks like we're
gonna have to deal with
some grade-A denizen garbage
to get out of here,
so let's split up
and make it quick.
Simon,
you're with me.
But I wanna be
with you.
So Simon and Tuba
can be...
So Simon
and Tuba can be friends.
Uh, all right.
Hazel's with me.
Ughhhh!
So I'm stuck with Tuba?
No, I'm stuck with you.
It's a good kind
of stuck.
Huh.
Why don't
you like Roy?
Well,
because Roy's a null.
What does that mean?
Null.
It means nothing.
Not even a zero.
Is it different
than a denizen?
Eh, null, denizen—
same thing.
Whoop-a-doop-a-doo!
What's wrong with nulls?
You can't trust them.
You never know
what they'll do.
But... have you ever
gotten to know one?
I don't need to, Hazel.
I can just tell, okay?
But Tuba is good.
Oh, well, Tuba is
one of the good ones.
Now,
how about some fun?
It's Green O'Clock!
Excited to meet you all
for the first time!
Will you move?
Hm?
Why not
take the ramp?
What are you
even talking about?
There's no ramp.
Ugh, just let me lead.
You are a child.
Even Bugle was more mature
than you.
Yes!
Got it!
Ugh!
The key is green.
How are we supposed to
get this to the red door?
It's Blurple O'Clock!
Step aside.
And, please,
cover your ears.
See?
Teamwork begins with
two people trusting each other.
Roy is at a 10,
and I need him
to be at about a 6.
Uh, so,
uh... who's Bugle?
Bugle is— w-was...
my daughter.
I'm, uh, lucky
Hazel came into my life.
It's Red O'Clock!
Door's back!
Any luck with a key?
Yes and no.
We need the clock
to be green.
Hazel: I went down a slide,
and it was fun!
Come on, Tuba.
Uh...
Let it be known,
I do not enjoy mazes.
Maze?
But the only maze
was green.
You're color blind.
Red and green
look the same to you.
Hm?
Tuba, get that key.
I can help with the maze.
Got it.
-Yeah! All right!
-Whoo-hoo!
Hip-hip.
You did it.
Hooray for teamwork.
Also, hi, I'm Roy, I'm your boy,
and I don't believe we've met.
Whoa!
One-One found us!
Throw Hazel across!
No, wait!
We've got you, Hazel!
I promise!
Shh.
Just take it easy-peasy.
My little lemon...
...squeeeeezy!
Tuba!
Get to the next car.
I'll go back for Tuba.
Teamwork begins with
two people trusting each other.
But you?
You're no person.
It's fine.
They'll be okay.
Where's Tuba?
Where is she?
Hazel, you're safe.
You never have to worry about
that null again.
I-I-Is she...?
Yeah, I wheeled her.
I know you might not
understand now, but trust me—
Hazel—
Ah, told ya
I could take her solo.
Let's see how high
our numbers got.
Ugh!
I thought
you'd be happy!
Hazel?
Hazel...