What's going on?
What's on me?
It's stuck on me!
It's my skin!
Why is it my skin?
I— I— I don't know!
I want Tuba.
She's... gone, Hazel.
N-No!
Let's go get her!
Hazel, she's not just gone.
She died.
What if I'm really,
really good?
I promise!
I won't do anything bad,
ever!
Please, Grace!
Please!
No, Hazel!
It doesn't have anything to do
with you being good or bad.
It's not like that.
It's not your fault.
I'm a train person?
Maybe?
I don't know.
Do you hate me?
No, Hazel,
why would you say that?
You hated Tuba.
No.
I didn't hate Tuba.
But Simon did.
Simon's going to kill me too!
Grace,
I'm afraid of the wheels!
No!
He won't!
We just—
won't tell Simon, okay?
He doesn't need to know.
So we can't let him see
the shell, okay?
You have to stay calm and
take big breaths, in...
And out.
You guys were out there
for a while.
Don't you ever take action
like that again
if I haven't given you
explicit orders!
Are you pulling rank on me?
Yes.
Yes, ma'am.
Hazel, let's go.
Hazel?
I wanna do something
before we leave.
What?
I...
wanna have a funeral
for Tuba.
A funeral?!
Hazel, Tuba isn't... here.
So it would be hard
to have...
There's no body left
to bury, kid.
Simon!
The train is ours,
not theirs.
That's how we do things,
Hazel.
I'm being good.
I'm being calm.
What?
It would be good for me to go!
To a funeral.
It helps to say goodbye.
But the Apex are just
a car away.
Let's let her do this.
I mean, do you really want to
throw her in with the Apex
when she's
still crying over a null?
I—
I guess that makes sense.
Yeah!
Of course it does.
Everything I do makes sense.
Okay, Hazel, Simon thinks this
is a great idea.
I want to find a spot that
Tuba would like.
Sorry to be the voice of reason
again, but there's no body.
Just say something about her
and we'll pretend a bunch
of annoying neighbors
brought casseroles
and be done with it.
This will be Tuba.
It's something that was ours.
Here?
No.
Bright out tonight, eh?
Or is it just me?
Take 'er easy!
Here?
Well, if you didn't want to come
here, you should have said so!
Oh, and I'm sure you wouldn't
have complained
about whatever choice I made?
Where would you have
picked then?
The lake.
We're rocks, Martin!
We can't swim!
I love it
when you get angry.
No.
And then the squirrel
scratched again.
"Where are my little seeds?"
Then louder, "Where are
my little seeds?!"
Boo!
Here?
No.
Ugh!
Just choose a spot!
Stop it!
You did this!
This is forever
and I'm going to do it right!
Hazel!
Ugh!
She's six, Simon!
Can't you take even one second
to remember
how you felt
when The Cat left you?
Fine.
Have the pretend funeral
for the pretend person.
But I'm waiting by the exit.
Hazel?
Hazel!
Hazel!!
Where are you?
I'm in the tree!
It's here.
Tuba wants to be high up
where she can see the sky
and be protected from rain
and animals and kissing rocks.
Tuba was really nice
and protected me
and gave me good hugs.
She made me feel like
I was warm all the time.
But not the kind of warm
that's outside
and makes you sweaty,
but, like, inside and comfy.
Oh, and thank you to her kids
for letting me have Tuba
because they were gone
and I needed her.
And maybe now Tuba
can be with them again
since she can't be with me
and I hope she likes that.
Grace, would you like
to say something?
Oh.
Umm, I don't—
I don't think I should.
Please?
Funerals have people
talk at them!
Okay, uh...
I didn't know Tuba well,
but she was very important
to Hazel.
Tuba was nice to me, too.
She was quiet,
but not in a bad way.
And she helped us
and was pretty brave and...
It's okay,
that was good.
Now I'm gonna sing a lullaby
that Tuba made up for her kids
and said it was
for me too.
Don't be a worry baby
No need to hurry, baby,
when you're with me
Don't run way up ahead
Take the long way instead
There's lots to see
When you slow down
to listen
Then you won't go a-missin'
chances to play
We'll always have tomorrow
No need to let it borrow
time from today
So don't be a worry-baby
No need to hurry, baby
When you're with me
Just take it easy peasy
My little lemon squeazy
You're always with me
Thank you for being with me,
Tuba.
I'm going to keep loving you
like you're still here.
Grace?
Yeah?
I have to go to the bathroom.
Done?
Great!
Let's go.
The Apex are still
in the next car.
We'll finally figure
your number out,
Hazel will assimilate,
we won't need to babysit her,
everything will be back
to normal.
Now you'll see how much better
it is to live with passengers.
And I'll even name a character
in my book after you.
A really brave one.
Would you like that?
Wow!
How cool is that, Hazel?
Wow.
Thank you, Simon.
Hmmm.
No sign.
Well, they're probably
further in.
How they've even survived
without us is just—
What?!
But it showed them in here.
It's not like
we passed them.
What have you kids been doing
to the train cars?