Wh— What?
The train cars,
genius.
I scanned this car
for aberrations and found nothing.
Then you're here
for all of one minute,
and I get an alert that there are lines of code
that don't match the reality of the car.
We've barely escaped
the ejecting train cars!
We're the victims here.
There are no victims.
There's a glitch
on the train.
One sent me out from the Engine
to resolve it.
One? Like One-One?
One-One-One.
The False Conductor!
He's been trying to kill us ever since
he took over the train from the True Conductor!
The true—
One has no idea you exist,
short pants.
At least no more so
than any of the passengers.
In a very real sense,
we're just numbers to him.
Ugh. Hang on.
Every passenger
is important.
Their well-being and progress
is what the train is all about.
All aboard the growth train,
toot toot, wheeeee!
.Sincerely, your conductor, One.-One.
Sincerely, your conductor, One-One.
You're weird.
Yes! I am!
Good heavens, you three really have
no idea what's been happening?
Ugh!
This is so tedious.
Some of the cars on the train
have corrupted code.
I created a pulse
that scans for that code.
And it was working fine
until three weeks ago,
when cars started ejecting one
after the other.
And since you say you keep
getting ejected along with them,
you're the only lead I have as to what's gone wrong.
So start talking.
You're the number cluster
we've been tracking!
You've been tracking me?
It hasn't been the Apex!
The what?
It was just a single
high number.
The highest
we've ever seen.
Maybe the highest
there's ever been.
Rude.
We have the highest numbers
of anyone on the train,
except you.
I don't care.
This isn't about my number. It's about my cars.
I need information.
The ejected cars, have there been objects
that didn't match the environment?
Phone booths?
College campuses?
A lot of turtles?
Too many turtles?
A number of turtles that makes you think,
"Why? Why turtles again?"
Grace!
That first shifter!
It had turtles.
Simon, here— now.
We have to get away from her.
What?!
She probably knows more about numbers
than anyone on the train.
She might know
what's wrong with yours.
Well... exactly!
She might not
just know something.
She might have something
to do with it.
She's working
with One-One,
and— and, um...
Code A17 of the Apex—
never trust
adult passengers.
Okay. Okay.
Right.
Is she looking at us?
What?
Where are you going?!
Ugh! I hate children.
This car
is marked for ejection!
You know I can tell
you children are in the car.
I can see your numbers
on the screen.
Ugh!
This interface is garbage.
Phew!
There!
We can camp
for the night.
Let's check
our numbers.
No change.
Let me see yours.
Ugh! Don't!
Yeah, don't!
Why?!
Because I don't
want to know yet!
I have to know
so when we go back—
Simon, enough!
This is happening to me!
Quit making it
all about you!
I say when I look at it.
I say what I do about it.
You need to back off
and give me some space!
Okay.
I, um...
I'll keep watch outside.
You guys rest.
Simon?
Yeah?
I...
Nothing.
Good thinking.
Hmm.
Hazel, what are you doing?
I'm mad!
You need sleep.
No!
He grabbed your arm!
He's being mean to you,
like Tuba!
Hazel, the shell!
Good!
I'll use it to fight him!
Hazel, shhh!
I don't care.
I can protect us
with it.
Hazel, come here.
I'll be Tuba now.
Okay. It's okay.
Stay close to me.
I'm Tuba.
Hey!
Simon, I presume.
You're gonna help me.
I am?
Well,
isn't that nice of me.
I want something that will tell me
what's wrong with Grace.
Oh, piffle.
I can do that.
One, she's very full
of herself.
Two, she has no respect
for personal property.
Three—
This isn't a joke!
You left me,
so give me something for Grace!
I didn't leave you, Simon.
I ran.
There's a difference.
No, there isn't!
That gohm almost got me.
I didn't realize you weren't by my side
until the next car.
But you never came back.
I...
No.
I am who I am, Simon.
I can't give you more
than that.
Could you give me
a few more details?
Something more helpful than,
"I need a thing?"
Grace's number
is broken.
Oh?
It's going down,
but she doesn't seem
to want to fix it.
And now we found this woman
who's working with One-One.
She has the highest number
we've ever seen!
It's almost up
to her neck!
But Grace doesn't even want
to talk to her!
She made us run!
The woman—
How old is she?
How should I know?
She's just...old.
And British.
Amelia.
Her name is Amelia.
We've had some
unpleasant dealings.
She tried to kill me
a few times, actually.
Though I suppose that
would only endear her to you.
She's dangerous.
I'd stay clear of her.
So...
Grace was right to run?
You Apex work so hard
to get your numbers up.
Doing what?
Destroying things,
pillaging cars,
playing soldier.
Think about
what it would take for Amelia to get
a number that high.
And as for Grace...
you're a smart boy.
Surely you've thought
about what the reverse means,
what would make
a number go down.
Numbers are power.
Numbers are numbers,
and they're supposed
to go down.
You say Grace's number
is broken,
but the truth is,
you just don't like
how it's working.
Th— That's not it!
I don't believe you!
You're lying!
I never lie.
You lie all the time.
Well, I never lie
when I'm telling the truth.
She's not acting
like she should!
And how exactly should
she be acting?
She's not one of your
miniatures, Simon.
She's shutting me out!
Please, Samantha.
I have to know why.
Very well.
The only way to find out
what she isn't telling you
is to see what
she isn't telling you.
What?
You'll have to extract tape
of her memories and go inside.
Since it isn't yours,
it's safe.
Going into your own tape,
however,
can be unpredictable
and dangerous.
I knew you'd have something.
You always do.
But, Simon!
What?
We shouldn't always know
what's in a person's mind,
especially the minds
of those we love.
I'm not a child anymore.
I know what I'm doing.
Oh, Simon...
...you have no idea.