You drooled on me in your sleep.
And how long have you been up?
Forever.
I had bad dreams...
Hey!
Stop it!
Why?
It's me.
Simon can't see you
like that.
Well, he isn't here.
Yeah...
Where is he?
Maybe he's waiting to regroup
on the gangway?
Huh?
Back off, lady!
Look,
I'm no good at this...
but I just saved your lives,
and, well...
Hello.
I'm Amelia.
Ugh.
You want eggs?
I'm making eggs.
Yes please!
Hazel!
Believe me,
I don't enjoy asking for your help.
But I need to understand
this anomaly.
I appreciate your cooperation,
Grace.
Wait. Y-Your number just went down!
Did it?
When a number's this high, a stray digit here
or there doesn't really make much of a dent.
How many eggs
do children eat?
Six n' a half!
That's how old I am!
Huh-unh.
Hmm...
Six-ish burnt eggs.
Probably should've mentioned
I'm not great at eggs.
Or... any food.
Nuh-uh, you make
the best pancakes!
It pains me to turn down
my first compliment in 33 years,
but we just met yesterday.
You've never had them.
I just know.
You and Alrick both.
What's an Alrick?
He was a person.
My person.
And I...
lost him.
I like you.
We're all here
for you.
Heartwarming.
But this car is marked
for ejection.
Time to go.
Not without Simon.
Ugh.
Fine.
Simon, where are you?
Grace, fall back!
You were right
not to trust her!
Whoa!
Simon!
Ugh...
Your belt!
You've taken our symbol!
What are you prattling on about?
You're corrupting the mark
of the Apex!
You mean this sine wave?
It's a sound shield, pipsquirt.
Wait, is that why you all
smeared lipstick on your face?
This mark represents
the True Conductor,
a man with the highest number
who wore a big black helmet with a red wave on it.
Yeah, and if he wasn't imprisoned
by the False Conductor, One-One,
he would eat you alive!
Tell me, so this man, he had
a face with a symbol on it
and, let me guess...
A voice like this?
If anybody was
a "False" Conductor,
it was yours truly.
You...
you...
Seven years ago
in the Pumpkin Car,
do you remember
saving a girl?
No.
Look I can reminisce all day,
but we simply must be moving on.
Find me in the next car.
We have to leave!
She is not our ally!
I...
I don't think she's the enemy,
either.
Yeah,
she knows about turtles!
Simon, that voice,
I haven't heard it since I was a kid...
that's what he...
she...
sounded like when I first
got on the train.
But Samantha told me she's—
Samantha?
You went back to The Cat?
Yes, but...
it's complicated...
Hey, it's okay.
I trust you.
But right now?
I need you to trust me.
Can ya do that, ponytail?
Hey!
Ho!
Whoa!
Brilliant.
It's reset.
We'll have to wait.
So what do you think?
I think they're sticks.
They're robots.
Oh.
My mistake.
So, um...
you were the Conductor, huh?
Yes, and no.
I was a passenger,
just like you...
but I didn't like
how One did things.
Lies!
So I took control.
Tried to recreate my old life.
Failed.
Again and again and again.
Created things that
never should have been.
Repeating pod propaganda...
Shh!
I made the cars I'm ejecting.
But One didn't fancy that,
so any car he didn't make,
I must quarantine.
So are you a prisoner of...
One-One, er... One?
Prisoner?
Of that little peanut?
No.
No, I'm making amends.
Maybe one day I'll even
get off this train...
Why would anyone in their right
mind want to get off the train?!
You know why you're here,
don't you?
To get the highest number.
The whole point of the train is
to work through your problems.
The worse you do,
the higher your number goes.
Until you get it down to zero...
you're trapped.
Lies!
The train is our right!
Simon, stop!
No, she's brainwashing you,
Grace!
She said it herself!
She's working with
the False Conductor!
Simon, listen to me.
She was the False Conductor!
Well...
well even if she was,
she's lost her way!
Whatever "way" you think I'm on
was never my "way!"
Have you ever considered
that you've been wrong?
Ha! Of course not,
you're a child.
Say it again!
Take off that shield belt
and say it again!
You have until the count
of three to stop
or I'll put you down.
One.
Simon, stop!
Stop it, stop it!
Two.
Simon!
Three.
I...
I can't believe it!
Of course!
The turtles!
It was just
a stupid handkerchief...
I got closer than I ever
imagined...
And this,
this was my number!
What are you talking about?
The girl's not a passenger,
she's one of my failed
attempts at making Alrick!
She's the anomaly!
So Hazel is a clone of your...
dead boyfriend?
No, not a clone.
Something... Something else.
I don't know.
I'm Hazel!
Debatable.
If the pulse I created passes
through any car with her inside,
it will be ejected.
I'll take it from here.
The girl needs to be quarantined
before the pulse returns.
Once the canyon fills,
you'll be able to exit.
Let's go— now.
Leave the null
with the old woman,
go around the outside,
get home.
Problem solved!
You aren't leaving me,
are you?
I'll leave
if I want to, null!
Huh?
Heh.
We should camp out
for the night, though.
Wait until the pit fills.
What is going on?
We can leave!
No! It's just safer this way,
Simon!
It's just safer, okay?
It's safer.
Uh...
Okay.
You're the leader.
Simon's going to kill me too!
Grace, I'm afraid
of the wheels!
No! No!
He won't!
We just
won't tell Simon, okay?
...just won't tell Simon, okay?
...won't tell Simon, okay?