Whoa!
I've been doing
a lot of thinking.
It was surprising,
to say the least,
to discover that
our friend Hazel is...
a denizen.
Just to remind you,
you do have a time limit.
I need to get this out, okay?
From what I understand,
Hazel will be a danger
to any car she enters.
As the leader of the Apex,
I have a group counting on me
to keep them safe.
And Hazel is part
of that group, now.
We don't leave Apex behind.
Hazel, you're sticking with us.
I don't want
to go with you.
Huh?
It's okay.
We can work around
the denizen thing.
I'm not going with you!
You said the Apex
is supposed to be brave,
but if that's true,
why are you all so...
scared of me?
Hazel, I—
Amelia?
You know stuff about me I don't.
I want to go with you.
Maybe I can learn.
Ugh. Well, you're certainly
coming with me,
but I'm not on a road trip.
What I'm doing here is my job.
I'm an inventor, an engineer,
a snappy dresser,
but I am not your caretaker.
Grace and Simon weren't, either.
I promise to
take care of myself.
Well, I suppose
you're worth studying.
Stand back.
The pulse will be hitting
any moment.
Hazel, it's not too late
to change your mind.
Good luck, Grace.
Finally,
things are back to normal.
Me and you—
like it's supposed to be.
No more Hazel holding us back.
Knock it off, Simon.
I'm not in the mood.
Really?
'Cause I'm feeling really good!
For the first time
in a long time,
things are right in the world.
You don't know
what you're talking about!
Hazel was our friend,
and you wrote her off
like she was nothing.
I was your friend first!
What is your problem?
What?
I'm...
home?
Huh?
What— What?
You know, Shayna,
you were right.
Chloe shouldn't smile
until her parents
can afford to get her braces.
What is happening?
Oh no, Grace.
Look at you.
I wanted to try
a different look.
We're hosting
Ambassador Morris tonight.
Julie?
Molly.
Jacob.
Susan.
I don't have time for this.
Take her to a movie,
or something.
Of course, Mrs. Monroe.
She'll have a fun day.
I'm sorry to tell you
that your daughter was caught
with a stolen bracelet
from Blassie's.
It seems she convinced her
little friends to do the same.
I'm sorry, too— because
you're obviously mistaken.
Dad, I'm sorry.
Just stay quiet,
and we'll fix this.
It's absurd to think that
our Grace would need to steal.
She's well provided for.
We raise her with morals.
We give her guidance.
[ Indistinct talking ]
I just wanted to be noticed.
The train knew you were wasted
in the real world.
It gave you a chance to go
somewhere you'd be respected.
Simon, are you doing this?
Take what we need
from the car.
I never thought I'd get to see
the Conductor with my own eyes.
He's perfect.
Everything finally
makes sense again.
That's... not right.
No, no, no.
I saw it before
you came in here.
This is fake.
So, my memories are real
until you don't like them?
Then, they're fake?
You're just using
Amelia's lies to trick me.
She was lying,
just like The Cat lied to me.
And you lied to me.
Everyone lies to me!
Samantha!
I can't fit!
I'm still out here, help!
You... saved me.
Oh... yeah.
I did.
Samantha left me.
Hey, it's scary here.
But you're fine now.
How'd you get it so high?
Oh!
I'm, like, really good
at the train.
I said it!
No, you didn't.
...and the Conductor
was huge!
Grace saw him!
He blocked out the sun!
But he gave us a chance
to save people like you.
You don't have to
be scared anymore.
The Apex stick together.
"Stick together."
It's nice to know I wasn't
the only one you lied to.
I wasn't lying!
We just won't tell Simon, okay?
He doesn't need to know.
So we can't let him see
the shell, okay?
Simon, it's more
complicated than—
We just won't tell Simon, okay?
I was trying to figure out...
If you let me explain...
We just won't tell Simon, okay?
You would have killed her!
Look, I'm sorry!
Is that what you want to hear?
Will that word fix it?
Do we get to dig through
your most painful memories next?
I didn't want it
to be like this.
I liked what we had.
But you made me do it.
You betrayed the Apex.
And you betrayed me.