I'm not going with you!
I don't want to go with you.
Huh?
It's okay, we can work on
the denizen thing.
What part of
"I'm not going with you"
don't you understand?
I'm not going with you!
You tried to control me,
just like you
control the Apex!
But I never meant to hurt you.
You killed Tuba!
No, it was Simon!
He didn't come up with the idea
to wheel denizens on his own.
It's your fault she's gone.
You think you're strong,
but you're scared.
A coward leading cowards!
Hazel, please, I didn't know.
And worst of all?
When you had the chance
to make it right...
I...
I can't believe it!
You protected yourself!
You tried to control me
and Simon instead of being honest.
You're wrong, Grace.
Wrong about numbers.
The Conductor.
Denizens.
Everything.
And you know it.
It's true.
I-I'm afraid.
Afraid of being wrong,
of disappointing others,
of not being enough.
I did everything to aVoid being alone...
and it's exactly how I ended up.
I'm so sorry, Hazel.
You deserved better.
Good luck, Grace.
Huh?
Oh!
You okay?
What?
That's as far as you go, Void.
Lucy! What's going on?
And... what's a Void?
You.
And we all know
how the Apex deals with Voids.
Well, I don't.
Simon told us everything.
Lucy, I—
Simon! Simon!
The Void infiltrated the car!
W-Wait, wait, stop!
It's just me!
What?
Look who came crawling back.
The Void that betrayed us all!
I didn't betray anybody!
Oh?
Then where's your mark?
Look, we've been
doing things wrong.
It's my responsibility
as the leader to—
Highest number!
I'm the leader now!
But Simon left me for dead!
Trapped in—
Your number speaks
louder than words, Void!
Okay, what is a Void?
What is a Void, Apex?
A leader who is
no longer fit to lead!
A danger to us all!
And how do we deal with Voids?
We wheel them! Wheel them!
Do it!
Wheel the Void!
Stop!
Let go!
Get off!
Stop! Okay, please don't do this!
Throw her off the train!
Wait, wait!
Did Simon even tell you
we met the Conductor?
Lies!
No, it's true!
She isn't the real Conductor,
she's just a woman named Amelia!
She didn't make the train, and...
she doesn't care about any of us!
Don't listen!
The Void is trying
to infect you with its lies!
Simon, I know you're hurt.
But I had to keep Hazel safe.
I've made a lot of mistakes,
but that wasn't one of them.
We've been doing it wrong.
We can still change!
Why would I ever want to change
if I'm always right?!
Let's get out of here!
Oh, this is not good!
You're an infection!
A rot!
A poison!
I won't let you take what's ours!
Simon, you're in a lot of pain.
I understand that.
Another hollow apology, Grace?
No.
I'm not responsible
for your problems.
I don't owe you anything!
You owe me everything!
Why did you...?
I...
I don't know.
Grace!
Huh?
Simon.
He's gone.
Huh?
This is the last thing I ever wanted.
But we know the truth,
and I can't ignore it.
We're all on this train
for different reasons.
But it's unfair for me to tell
you how to understand yourself.
I mean, I don't even
fully understand me.
But together, we can make some changes.
First change being...
we can't be the Apex anymore.
Then what are we gonna be?
Guess we'll have to figure it out?
Figure it out?
What's gonna happen?
What does that mean?
What?