What are you gonna do when I’m at game design camp?
Die of boredom, probably?
Ugh. Yes!
Way to abandon me in my time of need.
Sorry, Mikayla, but Oshkosh calls.
I’m the coding hero Wisconsin needs.
I don’t think they want their coding hero
to stink up the whole state with her onion breath.
Hey! It’s not my fault I have a sophisticated palate.
You have a gross palate.
I think I’m gonna work on my game
some more before I leave.
I wanna code those other nerds
into the ground.
I thought your game was cool
when I played it.
And you know how I feel
about video games.
You hate them.
I hate them.
But I like yours.
So...
When your dad picks you up for visits,
does he come in
and talk to your mom?
Uh, yeah, sometimes.
I guess it’s weird to see your parents
talking to each other now.
What do you mean, “weird”?
Well, ’cause, you know...
They’re not married anymore,
and everything is different.
It’s fine.
Lots of people’s parents are divorced.
Y’know, I better hurry home and pack.
I-I-I’ll see you on Monday.
Oh, okay. Bye!
Text me when you’re at camp!
You’ll do great!
Tulip?
Tulip, it’s your dad.
We need to talk to ya.
Nah, she went upstairs.
I don’t know, Andy,
what do you wanna do?
Okay, game. You’re supposed to
be working, but watch,
I’ll press play, and you’re just gonna die.
See, that’s not right!
Look at you!
You’re moving around now!
Don’t ever change.
Thanks, Coding is Cool guy!
“Why, thank you, Tulip,
for with your purchase of my book,
I can finally afford to have this ferret
removed from my face.”
Tulip? Can you come down here, please?
Ugh!
Yeah?
Tulip, I’m so sorry, but your dad
can’t take you to camp.
What?! What do you mean? You...
You said if I brought my grade up
in English, I could go!
You... You... You and Dad
signed a contract and everything.
I-I know, Bud.
But your dad mixed up the dates
and planned a work trip out of town.
Okay, well, then why don’t you take me?!
I have a 12-hour shift at the hospital tonight
and then another shift on Sunday.
I thought you’d be gone
the whole time.
What, so you’re both too busy
to be my parents?
Hey!
You guys are the ones whose divorce
keeps messing everything up, not me!
This isn’t fair!
No, it isn’t fair!
But it was an accident.
And your dad and I are still
trying to figure this out.
I know, we’re not very good at it yet.
Good at what?
Good at being divorced?
Tulip, I just mean scheduling.
What schedule?!
It’s two of you and one kid!
It’s not that hard!
Ngh. Fine.
Whatever. I can’t go.
Tulip, wait!
Let’s talk about this!
No! I’m going back to my game.
Ugh!
Huh?
300 miles is not “a quick hop.”
Oh! Well, that’s lucky.
What the—
Ugh, did I just hallucinate a train station?
Well, that’s... boring.
“Tulip, we missed you
at game design camp!”
“Oh, I’m sorry, I didn’t quite make it
because I decided to fall asleep in a field
and dream about outdated
modes of transportation!”
Are you my mum?
W-What?! What? Am I what?
Nooo!
So you’ve come to bring me
the sweet release of death?
Also no?
Are you a toy?
You have really good speech recognition.
I’m looking for my mother.
I dunno what she looks like, though.
She might be large...
Or small, like a nurturing bagel.
Are you looking
for your bagel mother, too?
No. Definitely not.
Not my dad, either.
Weird toy.
So what are you looking for?
I’m not looking for anything.
I’m going to Oshkosh.
Is that your home?
It’s where game design camp is.
So you’re going alone?
Yes.
Without your parents?
I don’t need them to get there!
Now go back to being a snowman,
or a... whatever you are!
Oh my gosh, what am I?
oooooh?Uuuuuugghhh...oooooh?
Pfft. North St. Paul kids
probably built this.
That door is impossible to open.
The only way out is through hypothermia.
Pfff.
This... is the train?
I’m on a big train?!
Like a... Like a really weird big train?!
You can reach doorknobs?!
How does this door work?
A-A-Are you, like, a real robot?
Are there other people on here?
Is this what trains are like?
Yes!
Yes to what? Which?
Wait. What’s in the next train car?
It’ll probably be disappointing.
Wow!
Oh...
Hmm.
Well...
Called it.
I wonder what this room’s for.
Whoa!
Back to being impressed!
Are you building a coffin?
I-It’s a character from my game.
I call it: Good Guys Poppin’ Bad Guys.
It’s the best game
I’ve ever made.
How many games have you made?
One.
You’re joking.
That’s... kind of a weird thing to joke about.
That’s my name!
!I’m One!-One...
I’m One-One...
And that’s kind of
a weird name to have.
Unlike my name, which is Tulip
and is perfectly normal.
Oh, you know I’m getting up there!
Ha-ha!
Ah!
Wh-What’s this?!
One-One?
Do you know what Wisconsin looks like?
All right, hold on.
Lemme think.
I wanna say it looks like...
this?
...No.
This is not Wisconsin.
Oookay.
Ahh! What happened to that guy?!
You’re in kind of
a bad place right now.
I’m not... I’m...
I don’t want to be
on this train anymore!
Wait! Are you my mum?
I forgot what you said last time.
Huh?
What are you singing?!
It’s a wacky getting-chased song.
I made it up.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I can help, Miss Tulip!
You can do that?
Ahhhh!
Ahh!
Gimme a wall!
All right, Good Guy,
pop that bad guy!
Uh, Bad Guy’s turn!
One-One, how’s that wall?
Well, it’s more
of a house instead of a wall.
Do you want me to start over?
I’ll just start over.
No! Don’t start over!
I forgot to make a roof.
Is that weird for a house? No roof?
This place has some stuff
that’s okay about it,
and some stuff
that could be better.
There has to be a way off this train
that won’t kill me.
Okay, everything has rules.
E-Even crazy things
have their own logic.
It’s a train, right?
Trains have conductors.
One-One, i-is there a conductor?
Please tell me you know the answer.
Conductor? Hmm...
I think we have one of those.
But he would most
likely be at the engine.
I’m getting off this train.