46 down.
7 letters...
One-One, how long
have you been doing this?
I've been helping
since the start!
I think it's
a pretty powerful message.
Aw.
One-One, right now
I gotta take care of this.
So you stay here,
and no more writing, okay?
Aye-aye, Captain!
Ooofff!
O-kay.
That's not weird.
They look so peaceful.
Shh.
6-inch voice.
Did you say 60-inch voice?!
-Spells!
No angry wizards!
The door
should be inside of...
There's the gutter.
Aah! Ooh!This is where I belong.
Huh?
Aah! Aah! Whoa!
I almost found
my mum that time.
And you got the 11th-highest
score in pinball!
Don't wanna be
in the top-10, though.
Too much pressure.
Uh! This isn't
a game to me, One-One.
We can still have fun.
Not when you have things
to do.
You work first so you get
to enjoy the fun later.
I help my dad
fix the go-karts,
I get to drive them
before he resells them.
Work first.
Okay, sometimes there was
pizza during the work.
And hose fights.
But all of that
was still under
the work umbrella.
Aah!
It was 115 before!
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Did I do something wrong?
Did I lose a point?
Am I being timed?
I've seen
that happen before.
When it reaches zero,
you're a gon--
You're gone forever!
I was talking.
That's it?
Nobody told me this number
was gonna change.
Nobody said anything!
Now I'm gonna die
on this stupid train
'cause there isn't
a stupid rule book!
You rule in my book,
Ms. Tulip.
Ugh!
I don't have time for this!
That's right.
Step right up.
There we go.
Say --
I didn't catch your name.
Randall.
That's a strong name.
A strong name
for a strong man.
An effluent man
such as yourself
can turn his pile of junk
into donuts
with this
truly miraculous product --
the Donut-Holer!
That kinda
just looks like a pipe.
I'll demonstrate.
Presto! Donut!
This hat?
Bon appetít!
Donut.
Am I going too fast for you?
I get to be in charge
of selling these Donut-Holers?
I can start my own business?!
Yes! Why, you could have
a whole sales team
selling
these Donut-Holers --
with pioneers like us
right at the top!
Yeah, like a pyramid scheme!
Don't think of it so much
as a pyramid scheme
as a pyramid team.
You don't even know
the best part.
This is
the only Donut-Holer
certified
by my close, personal...
acquaintance,
the Conductor.
Conductor?!
H-Hey!
I'm supposed to be going
to Oshkosh.
It's this place
in Wisconsin.
And, also, my name is Tulip.
I should've said that earlier.
But there's
a game-design camp,
and my parents
signed a contract,
and I ended up
on this stupid train,
and I don't want
any of this!
My goodness, kitten!
One step at a time.
This number
keeps going down,
and if it reaches zero,
I'm done for.
I just want to find
a way off this train,
and you said
you know the Conductor.
You have to help me
before I die.
Tell me, kitten,
what makes you think
the digits
below your digits
are counting down
to your death?
Uh...One-One told me?
Mum check!
Hmm. Much too furry.
Or not furry enough.
Mother check?
C'est intéressant.
Yeah,
he's looking for his mom.
But...my number...
We'll get there.
Patience.
Excuse me, white ball.
Is this donut hat your mother?
Mmmmmm...yes?
Mm. And, tell me,
if I put this donut hat
on my head, will I die?
Sure. Why not?
Charming fellow, but not
the most reliable, is he?
Wha-- One-One!
You made me think
I was gonna die!
It would be surprising
if you never died.
Ugh.
I'm sure the Conductor
would be just
as sympathetic to your plight.
I'd rush off to see him
right now,
but, unfortunately,
my personal shuttlecraft
has been grounded.
You have a shuttlecraft?
I'd fix her myself,
but...you know...
no thumbs.
I have thumbs.
I don't know anything
about shuttlecrafts,
but I fixed some stuff
with my dad.
There's still
the issue of...
my payment.
Payment?
Even with my craft,
it will take a week,
maybe two,
to get to the Conductor.
That's a lot of sales
I'm missing out on.
I have...$12.42.
But one of the pennies
is Canadian.
Money doesn't have
much value to me.
I've always been more interested
in the peculiar and unique.
You know, I could take
the little white ball
off your hands.
In exchange, I will speak
to the Conductor
about getting you to...
Where was it again?
"Wis-con-sohn"?
One-One? You want to take
One-One with you?
Ms. Tulip,
we made so many donuts!
D'oh!Do you really need him,
or do you want
to get off this train?
Deal.
What kind of your own boss
do you want to be?
I don't think
I like that word "boss."
I want to feel like we're
all on the same team.
Team Randall!
Ms. Tulip,
how tall are you?
Oh, I'm about...What is your hair?
How am
I supposed to answer that?
Is your name Tulip
because you have a bulbous head?
What? No.
It was when I was born.
There were complications.
Oh, no!
Did you make it out alive?
Uh, yeah.
It was some kind
of breathing issue.
But I bounced back like a
"perennial flower" or something.
At least that's
what my mom told me.
So you could have been named
after any perennial plant?
Like horseradish?
No! I don't know.
I didn't name me.
Look, Ms. Tulip.
It's you.
That's a daisy.
I may not know
what anything does,
but there is a gear thing here
that isn't in there.
Do you know where we can get
a replacement?
Oh! I know,
I know!
Welcome to the Market!
Soak up your troubles!
Metal squid attack got you down?
Shop your cares away!
Put a little wiggle
in your step!
-Ooh!
-Ah!
Oh, yeah.
Oh, very cute.
I think she's cute, too.
Ugh.
How -- How much
for that gear over there?
Ah, expensive taste.
Hold the sponge!
Now, that's
a handsome-looking flower.
You mean my personal,
heartfelt gift
that I picked out for
my personal, heartfelt friend?
Ah, sounds valuable!
Oh. I mean,
it's not really for sale.
Too late. Now that I've seen it,
it's the only thing I want.
Oh, the price we pay
for the things we desire most...
Ugh! Fine!
Just take it!
My mechanical heart
breaks again.
I hope the warranty's
still good.
Shall we?
Well, One-One...
this is goodbye.
A new adventure!
Where shall
we meet again?
We...shall'nt meet again.
I'm leaving the train.
I can't take you with me,
but you'll be with the Cat now,
and she seems nice.
Oh.If it helps you
on your journey,
I understand.
Sit tight,
and I'll have the Conductor
sort out
this whole mess.
Goodbye forever,
Ms. Tulip!
Uggghhh!
How would you like to try
an exciting --
Not now!
Okey-dokey.
No need
to lose enthusiasm.
Just need
a different marketing audience.
Oh, wait a second!
I've got vision,
my good man,
and that vision
needs a team.
Well, I've never been
a part of a team.
Oh, it sounds
easy and profitable.
When I started Team Randall
38 minutes ago,
the mission statement
was "always be there
for each other."
It's more complicated
than that.
Is it?
Oh! Great job asking
the hard questions, Randall.
Oh, thanks, Randall.
You may not always bring in
the sales numbers I want,
but you've got heart, and
I feel like you care about me.
I didn't not care!
The cat was gonna help
One-One, too!
Probably.
I don't know.
I guess I don't really know
anything about the Cat.
I just...
wanted
to get off the train.
Listen up, Randalls.
If you can get me
to the Cat,
I'll take
your Donut-Holer thing.
Hot dog!
Hop in my body. It's not
as weird as it sounds!
Turn here
real quick!
Cool! Gum!
Aah! Oof!
I changed my mind!
I want One-One back!
Sorry, kitten.
We had a deal!
Ms. Tulip!
One-One,
I shouldn't have --
One-One!
Aah!
Uhh! Up and over!
Aaahhh! Ooh!
Oh, yeah!
One-One!
Can you slip
in the cracks?
"Slip In The Cracks"
is my middle name --
Randall Slip In The Cracks
Randall.
Wow!
You know, you really are
a smart cookie.
[ Randalls all speaking
at once ]
Aah!
Aaaahhh!
Good going.
Ms. Tulip!
You just made
a big mistake!
Good luck
getting off this train now.
-Have I got a deal for you!
-Aah!
Say, there,
you look like a smart gal.
This Donut-Holer is...
I'm so sorry
I gave you to the cat.
I was just scared I would
never get off the train,
and you made me think
I was gonna die,
and that doesn't
make it okay.
But you care,
and you're a good friend,
and I appreciate that,
and that makes me care,
and I just --
And I-I just...
I'm sorry.
It's okay, Ms. Tulip.
I knew you'd bounce back.
Just like when
your parents hatched you.