Still 109.
It's been a week.
Why won't you change?!
Are we stopping to talk
to our hands now?
Hello, hands!
Wait, do I even have hands?
Uh! That cat wasted time I could
have used getting off the train.
We've gotta keep moving if we're
ever gonna find the conductor.
From now on, we're not stopping
for anything!
All right, One-One, time me!
Ready!
-Set!
Hmm.
Ahem!
Oh, yeah.
Uh, go.
Look at me!
I'm a musical genius!
So many ducks.
Can you help me
find my normal eyes?
Sorry, no time!
So we mash...
Mash with us!
Nope, no time!
Huh?
-Got the time?
-No time!
You're telling me?
I'm dead!
Huh?
Look!
More weird, furry ducks.
Help me find the exit,
One-One.
Salutations, two-legged stranger
and loud-ball creature.
Welcome to Corginia.
I am Atticus,
King and Uniter of
the Cardigans and the Pembrokes.
I extend to you my greetings.
Hi, I'm Tulip.
I like...
books?
Greetings, Tulip the Literate!
Let me show you my kingdom.
Oh, no!
It's okay, I'm actually in kind
of a rush to find the e--
And so commences the official
tour-ginia of Corginia!
Does he do that a lot?
Oh, yes, every chance he gets.
Nope, no, no, no, no!
Down, down!
Go get it!
Please excuse us.
We just get very excited
when someone new comes
through the door.
Food dispensers,
belly-rub machines,
gift of speech?
You guys are doing pretty well
for yourselves.
Wow!
This is my first time
being nauseous!
Wow! How many dogs are there
in Corginia?
We're 400 strong, and 399 cute.
Just don't tell that
to Ugly Irwin.
Ugh!
Can I interest you
in a sunbeam to lie in?
Uh, nah.
One-One and I really need to--
Wait.
One-One?
The sun's gonna burn out
one day.
Enjoy this while you can.
No more sunbeams,
no more distracting,
but admittedly-fun dog stuff.
It's exit time.
Where is it?
Across the great river
and through the twisting
Woods of Mystery,
you shall find
the unsolvable puzzle door.
Water, woods, door.
Got it!
Thanks, King-dog.
Bye!
It's Atticus, and I must
urge you to wait.
One-One, time me.
Ready!
-Set!
Yay!
Shadow puppets.
Look -- I can make an eagle!
What is that thing?
It is the monster.
Quickly, Tulip -- to the temple!
♪♪
I will admit,
there are some things
I haven't told you
about Corginia.
Like why there's
a giant shadow monster?!
Yes.
Patience, young lady.
Patience? I'll never get to
the conductor
by just waiting around.
Let's band together
and attack the monster!
Impossible.
Ever since it appeared,
the water has risen
and ruined our city.
If we try to cross the harrowing
two-foot depths,
we would surely drown.
Everything is going paws-up
around here...
if you'll excuse the language.
Let me see if it's gone yet.
One-One, be careful!
Agh!
Looks like I'll have to start
writing his obituary.
Awfully morbid little thing,
aren't you?
-Yes.
-Agh!
Aah! What is it, One-One?It's gone!
I'm excited -- ahh!
Let us be on our way.
Didn't you want to go outside?
Yes. No.Outside? Outside?
Well... Maybe.Outside? Come on!
Wanna go outside right now?!Well, well, no!
Do you wanna go outside?Yes, I wanna go outside.
One week ago, that was the
Dog-partment of Water and Power.
Now it's just the Dog-partment
of Water and Water.
Wait, a week ago?
That's how long it's been
since my number changed!
Maybe that monster is related
to my number,
and maybe if we stop it
and reach the exit door,
he'll help me get off the train.
That's a lot of maybes.
Maybes are maybe
my favorite maybe.
Maybe.
-One-One, time us.
We're going in.Wait!
You'll need my help
if you intend to leave.
The exit is blocked
by the un-solvable puzzle door,
and it's too dangerous
to rush in alone.
Pfft.
How dangerous can it be?
I've faced a bunch of weird
stuff on this train.
Some were scary,
but others were dancey!
Dancing is scary.
I assure you, the monster
does not dance.
Tulip, I don't usually beg
unless it's for
a tasty-tasty treat,
but it seems we have
overlapping problems.
Will you take me with you so
that I may help save Corginia?
Ugh!
Fine.
As long as you
don't slow me down.
Excellent.
I must warn you, however,
we Corgis
are a proud people,
and we hate being picked up.
Why would you need
to warn me about that?
Stop! Ugh!
Please stop doing that!
Stop wiggling for two seconds!
Huh?
Phew!
It's the door!
Look out!
Aah!
Wait...
Aw!
It's just a little spider,
building her little spider web.
Ugh![ One-One laughing ]
We're grossed out, right,
Miss Tulip?
We've destroyed the monster.
I thought victory would
taste less musty.
Hmm.
I also thought the water level
would go down.
Yeah...
But maybe my number...
Of course!
Yeah, of course!
Nothing happened.
No water, no number, no monster.
Correlation isn't causation,
I know that!
Oh! I want some answers
for the first clue
I've gotten this whole time?
No!
Not allowed!
Miss Tulip?
I could travel for years on this
ridiculous train
and never escape.
Why is this thing on my hand?
It's not fair.
I'm going as fast as I can,
but I'm getting nowhere.
Just because you can't figure
out things immediately
doesn't mean
it won't happen eventually.
Yeah, but it feels like
every time
I find something logical
about this train, it's...
thrown back at me,
and I'm stuck without answers.
We can't always force progress,
Tulip.
After all, I didn't have
a solution
to Corginia's problems
until you showed up.
You helped me, Tulip.
Thanks, Atticus.
Now, I'm not just laying
on my back for nothing.
Okay.
Wait.
How could a spider cause
that problem
with the water?
The shadow came from
that weird orb,
but...
what's that weird orb for?
Hmm?
It's the real monster.
Those orbs must have something
to do with the environment.
We should attack.
We'll never make it.
Maybe we can escape out
the unsolvable puzzle door.
How do I unlock it?
First, you put your paw
on the handle.
Okay.Then you turn it.
All right.
That's how all doors open!
My people have been working on
this technology for decades!
Let's just talk to it.
-No!
-Hello! Oh!
Agh!
Atticus!
Corginia!
Agh!
Return to your seat!
Huh?
Unh!
You're awfully shooty today.
Somebody needs to spend more
time in the monster dance car.
Huh?
Oh, you're okay.
I'll just keep your obituary
on file then.
My number changed.
Hooray!
Wait -- is that good?
I'm not sure.
And I think that's okay for now.
Corginia will never be safe with
that monster still at large.
Since you're headed
in the same direction,
I request to accompany you
on your journey
so that I may hunt it down
and bring it to justice.
Also, you give
stellar belly-rubs.
Ha, ha!
It would be an honor
to be joined by such royalty.
Hooray! King Weird Furry Duck
is joining our team!
Wait, Miss Tulip?!
Don't you want me to time you?
Nah.
Uh? Aren't you coming?Yes!
Then, come on!No, ho-ho, no, no, no, no!
Ugh! We're not doing this
for every door!
You wanna go outside?Yes! No! Well...
Good king!No -- maybe!
You can do it!Yes, I want to go outside.