The door unlocked
a few minutes ago.
Mwah!
We'll miss you, Nancy!
We know your restaurant
will be a big success.
You've come a long way
in your pasta-making.
Oh.
Okay, so let's break down
the Straight-Up Italy Car.
I thought we agreed to call it
the Mediterranean Republic Car.
There were at least two things
that happened in there
that correspond
to what we did in Corginia.
We helped someone: Nancy.
And we fought someone: the mean grandmother
stealing coins from the fountain.
But there was no change
to my number!
See, if you look at the logic tree I've drawn...
Ooh, I like that you use circles
on your ‘i’s instead of dots.
Hmm.
Whoa.
Wow!
Anyway, my number...
May I suggest you give yourself
more moments of repose
in solving the mystery of your number?
Perhaps if you sleep on it,
the answer will come to you.
I can crack this!
I just have to go about it
using the Scientific Method.
Interesting bit of Tulip trivia:
I competed in North-Middle Branch Area
Middle School's Scientific Odyssey Trials.
My team even took home
the award for
Best Hypothetically-Proven Hypothesis.
At the very least,
give One-One a break from it.
Your logic trees have him more skittish
than a squirrel at a Corgi sock hop.
Ah!
I deserved that.
All right.
I'll put the notebook away—for now!
Until later, my love.
Ew!
Oh, cool!
Anyone see a door?
Maybe it's, like, one of those
where we have to push a knot,
like a secret passageway?
Because my admittedly petite,
but noble legs keep me close to the ground,
I have often found that
if there is not an answer in front of you,
one may come from above.
Right again!
If anyone's keeping track,
I think I'm winning
at being right about things.
I've been keeping track, and you are!
Maybe we should try
building a ladder.
Oh! Hi!
Do you know how we can
get to the door up there?
Ah, great!
Would you mind telling us how?
It can't speak!
Just like Atticus.
Huh?
Ugh, man.
This is gonna take a while.
And then the steps
that lead to the door were stolen
by a... giant spider...
made... of metal?
Huh?
Oh, like my spindly friend in Corginia.
One-One, that thing wasn't your friend.
Goodness!
Was it my mum?
It was trying to hurt us.
The question stands.
A new stairway can emerge...
but only if we put our paws
on this crystal.
And...
Eat some air!
Eating air makes me burpy.
I don't think you can breathe.
You never take my psychosomatic
conditions seriously.
Oh! Do we have to sing?
Hmm. Big heart?
Very emotional, perhaps. Or important?
My people have a song
about a folk-hero of ours:
The Ballad of Mustard and Stink Tail!
It's got drama, pathos,
and a bit of bawdy humor.
The crystal doesn't recognize howling?
But it's the ancient language of my people!
Ooh, ooh, me now! Me now!
Ahem.
Do-do-do-do-do-doot.
Connection failed.
Don't worry, guys!
I know a super emotional song to try.
High, low
Wherever we go
I just know that our souls twine as one
But that song is super emotional!
It's from this movie about a couple
who fall in love on a zeppelin,
and the guy dies
when the zeppelin blows up!
Okay. My world has a billion songs.
I'll find one that works.
Get ready, car,
because I'm about to blow your heart's mind!
I cleave thee
To mine heart
Girl, you know it's so true
That I'm in love with you
And even my pickup misses your face
I hope you choke
On her perfect cookie-cutter world
I can see our future children
When I look into your eyes
Ugh!
I like the ones about
unrequited love the most.
It's like, real, you know?
Perhaps if we sleep on it,
the right song will come to you.
You know, you suggest
we sleep on things a lot.
I am a dog.
Oh, right.
Well, maybe if we just build a ladder.
I'm sorry, but your weird
song thing isn't working.
Now, are you guys gonna help me
build a ladder or what?
Ugh! No thumbs!
Lot of help everyone is in this car.
Since I couldn't sing it,
this provides the perfect opportunity to tell you
The Ballad of Mustard and Stink Tail.
Ahem.
Once, a mighty Corgi
emerged from the Blue River.
He towered at a gargantuan
two-and-a-half feet tall.
The shrewd Stink Tail
stole all the bully sticks,
and when the pups awoke
for the Spring Festival of Plenty,
not even a kibble lay by the hearth.
At a stalemate, Mustard
and Stink Tail began trading,
not even a kibble lay by the hearth.
At a stalemate, Mustard
and Stink Tail began trading,
not even a kibble lay by the hearth.
At a stalemate, Mustard
and Stink Tail began trading,
not even a kibble lay by the hearth.
At a stalemate, Mustard
and Stink Tail began trading,
not even a kibble lay by the hearth.
At a stalemate, Mustard
and Stink Tail began trading,
not even a kibble lay by the hearth.
At a stalemate, Mustard
and Stink Tail began trading,
not even a kibble lay by the hearth.
At a stalemate, Mustard
and Stink Tail began trading,
not even a kibble lay by the hearth.
At a stalemate, Mustard
and Stink Tail began trading,
not even a kibble lay by the hearth.
At a stalemate, Mustard
and Stink Tail began trading,
not even a kibble lay by the hearth.
At a stalemate, Mustard
and Stink Tail began trading,
shall I say,
some rather salty jibes.
And from that day on,
when one saw Mustard the Shiny,
they also saw Stink Tail—
best friends to the end.
To the end of what?
Well, their lives.
Nice.
Guys, I'm done.
Man, that story is really, really long.
Mustard's story cannot be abridged.
Grump all you want,
but this is gonna work.
Yes! No more emotional songs.
Sorry, buddy, sometimes
you just gotta go logical.
Oh, no.
No! No, no, no, no, no, no!
It's locked!
No! That makes no sense!
I tried out every possible emotional theme
to find one that would work.
Break-ups, celebrities singing
to draw attention to important social issues,
even songs about
going after your dreams.
Like my dream of getting
to game design camp,
which is probably over,
like, forever ago.
I don't even know
how time works on this dumb train!
My heart, me singing.
Not your heart,
not you singing.
I thought I was
supposed to find a song
that made the crystal
feel something.
It has to be a song
that's emotional for me?
I've already liked a bunch
of the songs I've tried.
How would I know which song
I really connect to most?
Hmm.
I thought of The Ballad of Mustard
and Stink Tail immediately.
So it could just be
the first song I think of?
That's too arbitrary!
Seems worth a try.
Okay.
But if this were
the Scientific Odyssey Trials,
this would not win an award.
Not even for
"Best Last Ditch Effort."
And yes, that is a real thing,
and yes, I petitioned
to remove the category,
and no, they didn't.
Fine! I'm singing!
La-la-la-la...
What do I care about? Uh...
Programming is cool, and...
I like my friends, and, um...
onions, and...
the first three bites of pancakes, and...
Oh, I like getting new textbooks at the beginning
of the year before I'm sick of school again,
and road trips, and...
Huh. Road trips.
Heh.
Huh?
What?
Ugh, that's embarrassing!
Lemme pick a different one.
That doesn't make sense!
Doesn't seem to matter
if it makes sense.
I can't believe
this is happening.
It's the music of your heart.
But it isn't emotional at all.
It's just some song my family
used to sing on road trips.
It's about... dancing or something.
Gross.
Don't listen to him, just sing!
Yo, pretty ladies around the world
Got a weird thing to show you
So tell all the boys and girls
Tell your brother, your sister
And your momma too
'Cause we're about to throw down
Your heart is fun, Miss Tulip!
And you'll know just what to do
Wave your hands in the air like you don't care
Glide by the people as they stop to look and stare
Do your dance, do your dance
Do your dance quick, mama
Come on baby, tell me, what's the word?
Oh, word up!
Huh?
Uh...
Whoa!
Huh.