Thank you!
We'll never forget you!
What was that fella's
name again?
I kind of
already forgot.
Well, I'm gonna call him
Mildred the Tyrannosaur.
Aah!
So, cars on the train
can just move around?
I like it!
Feels wild and unpredictable.
Ohh!
What is this place?
It looks
to be a study.
What are they studying,
hoarding?
Hey, get out of there.
What? Me?
No, of course
not, no.
Hello, me-shaped
thing! Are you my mom?
And if so,
where have you been?
Rude.
If it isn't my favorite person
named after a flower for no good reason.
Calm down, dog.
Is this the cat
you told me about?
Unfortunately, yes.
She's a real gem.
One-One, last time we saw her,
she tried to kidnap you.
Kidnap?
Je n'oserais jamais!
I seem to recall we had a deal,
you backed out,
I left you alone,
and you abandoned me
to the relentless splashes
of a thousand Randalls.
Litter under the box.
Fine.
What are you doing here?
Me? Why, you're the ones
who oafishly stumbled
into my humble abode.
Nice place,
but your mom's a little quiet.
Don't touch that!
I apologize.
Everything here is
extremely important to me.
Yeah, well, it's really dusty
and boring to me,
so we're leaving.
Good-bye,
former kidnapper!
I miss you already,
and it's emotionally confusing.
Wait! Don't you want to explore
the kismet
that brought us
together?
Nope.
I don't trust you.
That prickles my whiskers,
kitten, but I understand.
Au revoir.
Oop!
Oh, my!
Be a dear and help me with
those fallen items, would you?
I'd do it myself,
but, well, you know.
Wait. Where
did you get this?
I procure so many
wonderful things.
Why?
Because...
i-it has my name on it.
Oh, is that one yours?
I suppose we ought
to give it a look, hmm?
Great idea!
Careful, Tulip.
I don't trust it.
Ooh, what
if it's important?
Of course it is.
This tape contains everything
that makes you you.
Every passenger has one.
Every passenger?
Guess you're not special.
Yes, and every one of them
has a little number
from a little tape,
just like you.
How's this connected
to my number?
Who made it?
How does it help me?
My dear, it will be much simpler
if we just watch.
Uh...
In you go.
I'm not sure
about this.
Huh?
Maybe you shouldn't --
Atticus?!
Aah!
One-One?!
Huh?
I remember that.
Oh, no!
Are you okay, honey?
Corn Nutters!
Bucket! Bucket!
Bucket!
Mom, look!
I can see Orion's belt...
and part of his pants.
Aww!
Aah!
Hey. You're me.
Wave your hands in the air
Like you don't care
What's going on?
Whoa! DolphWorld?
Oh, I used to love
this place!
I wonder why it closed.
Oh, Tulip, how about
those dolphins?
They look so beautiful
in their natural state.
A pyramid!
Oh, yeah!
This day was so much fun!
I'm home!
I'm...
still in a memory.
Are you tired of owning things
that aren't doughnuts,
but could be doughnuts?
Every day
of my miserable life.
Then buy
a Doughnut-Holer!
Easy to grip,
and certainly not a scam.
Ha-ha!
Certainly not a scam?!
Say no more!
I'm spending my life
savings on it!
So, you're tucking me in now, huh?
What was that?
Great news, bud!
You got a full scholarship
to Vassar,
the school for smart people
too creative for their own good!
Ah, that's better!
But who cares
about school?
Step aside, Shigeru.
You just became
Ultra-Galactic World President
of game design!
Who wants to celebrate with
double-onion ice cream cake?
Me!
This isn't right.
Something's
changing my memories!
Aah!
Get it off! Get it off!
Get it off!
Tulip, how about
those dolphins?
They look so beautiful
in their natural state.
A pyramid!
This isn't how it happened.
Uh...let's hear it
for Dolphmu!
What do you mean
she won't wake up?
Oh. So, that's why
they closed DolphWorld.
Mom, Dad,
can we move closer?
See? I told you
she needed glasses, Andy.
Well, maybe you should've taken
her to the optometrist, Megan.
When? When
am I supposed to do that?
Oh, yeah.
They were fighting. Hmm.
Any time. You can do it literally any time.
Okay, I'll be sure to add it
to my free time
between my double shifts
at the hospital.
Look, it's not like I'm just
sitting around watching TV...
Why'd the static go down?
Hmm?
Ah-ha!
Doughnut-Holer!
They shouldn't be here.
Harry the Bike Guy!
He's woke for the spokes!
It isn't a sham, I am.
Dad was there.
So,
you're tucking me in now, huh?
Awful news, Tulip.
We're getting divorced!
Aah! Aah!
Divorce! Divorce!
Divorce!
No! This isn't
what happened, either!
We having dinner here
or going out?
Neither.
We just want to talk to you.
Talk with you.
She gets it.
This is how it happened.
Tulip, we want you to know
we both love you so much, but...
things are going to be
changing soon.
Changing?
Uh, is this like
a puberty thing?
'Cause if so, I'm fine!
Let's just go get
Chinese food and --
Tulip, sit.
Andy.
What?
You might have noticed
Dad and I have...
problems, sometimes...
like arguments,
things like that.
We've tried to fix things,
but your Mom and I
decided to take some time off
from each other.
Are you...okay?
Yeah.
Why wouldn't I be?
You're not.
Are you...
getting divorced?
Uh, well...
right now,
we're just separating.
But then you're gonna
get divorced after that.
"It's not
that simple."
It's not
that simple, bud.
Yeah, it is. You're
either married or your not.
What else is there?
Tulip, please.
We just want you to know
that none of this is your fault.
I know that!
Why would it be?!
Oh. I remember
how scared I was.
Tulip, I'm so sorry.
How mad I was.
How alone I felt.
Things change,
but our love for you won't.
We just want you
to understand --
I understand
perfectly!
Things were fine, but then you
decided to change everything!
That's definitely
what happened.
But knowing it sure
doesn't feel any better.
I guess...I was the one
changing my memories.
Whoa!
Watch that tape without
thoroughly sniffing it first!
Why, look at that!
Awake already.
You tried to trap me!
Can one really be trapped when
reliving such happy memories?
Perhaps you want to sit down
again, give it a closer look?
I saw everything
I needed to see.
Let's not be hasty,
my petulant perennial!
What about your number?
I don't care.
But it's going down!
The train must think
you're doing well.
Oh, wow!
So, it's a good thing
my number's going down?
I'm growing as a person?!
Thanks, Train!
So glad an inanimate object
likes me!
No more numbers,
no more mystery.
We don't like you.
Where is the passenger?
Um, she isn't exactly here
at present.
And she may have taken
the ball with her.
The tape!
It should have trapped her!
Mercy, please!
You know I'm
the only one who can help you...
find...them!
Thank you.
I will not disappoint.
Do not fail again!
No. No!
My -- My things!