Ahh. I think it's safe to say
we took care of that spa car.
Sorry we had to bail
on that salt scrub,
but if we want to get anywhere,
we got to keep moving.
I'll never get
my youthful glow back.
Atticus, you holding up?
I think your people may have
a different definition
of relaxation.
They didn't even give us
kerchiefs when we were finished.
We aren't going to
stress ourselves out.
We're gonna stay positive,
and we are gonna take this
one car at a time.
When you scrub up,
you lift your heart up
You gotta be clean,
clean, clean
But when the...clean
is...clean...
First things first,
let's check for danger.
No spikes, mummies...
emotional manipulation.
Whoa!
Whoa-ho-ho!
Neat!
Gravity car?
My goodness.
I've always suspected stairs
can't be trusted.
One-One, you okay?
Oh! Uh...it's broken!
I broke it.
W-What do you --
I think
the inhabitants found us.
But did they send ambassadors
or warriors?
Royalty!
Gravity...turtle car?
Announcing
his supreme excellency!
Please, extend your necks
in adoration!
Hmm.
I am Aloysius III,
Emperor and Unifier of the Hard-
and Soft-Shelled.
Tacos?
Turtles.
Tsk! Come now,
Tulip. Ugh!
So, who will be
announcing whom?
Oh, uh, I'm Tulip.
I feel like I've done
this before.
Anyway, we're just looking
for the exit.
Let's not be hasty.
I don't often get to see
other royalty.
I am Atticus,
King and Uniter of the Cardigans
and the Pembrokes.
You'll pardon my lack
of fanfare,
but I am on a crusade
for justice
that requires
a bit of discretion.
Naturally. We can show you
to the other door,
but, pray tell, who is
your little friend
dismantling
our turtle-totter?
One-One,
what are you doing?
It was going "tch tch,"
but it should be going
"woop woop."
Shouldn't take too long.
Oh, I'm sure they have someone
who can fix it,
some kind of
licensed technician...
turtle -- turt-nition?
Tur...
Anyway, come on.
We got to go.
[ Groans ]
We Corginians pride ourselves
on our masonry.
I like to think that our stones
are sturdy and handsome,
like the corgis
that crafted them.
Gravity...turtle...
college car?
Structures can be
impressive,
but a culture is measured
by its cuisine.
Our all-natural jam pond
is both delicious
and great
for traveling quickly.
Intriguing.
[ Groaning ]
One-One, stop being
a fussy baby.
Look at that house!
There is no wall at all!
So?
These houses are supposed
to have walls!
Anyone could
just walk in!
Oh, my gosh.
I can see their saucepans!
We've ridden
a French-toast ferryboat
across a maple-syrup river.
This is relatively normal.
But those weren't broken.
Why do you --
I believe this is the door
you're looking for?
Cool. Well, uh,
Your Highness,
thank you so much
for taking us here.
We wish you
the best and --
Hey! One-One!
Come back!
We got to go!
Actually, Aloysius and I
were in the middle
of some fascinating
discussions.
How do you keep your crown
balanced on your head?
Bobby pins, mostly.
Hmm!
Knowing we have
a potential ally here,
perhaps we could
take our time?
We already spent a lot of time
in that spa car.
We need to get --
Hmm?
Hey, no.
Don't do that.
Why? I just want to know
what you're thinking.
No!
Stop it!
Hmm? Hmm?
Ugh! Fine!
We know
where the door is,
so I guess it wouldn't hurt to
stay for a little while.
Fantastic!
Now, my friend,
the charter of walkies dictates
that no citizen can be denied a stroll...
Meet back here
in one hour!
Hey, buddy.
I'm kind of worried
about you.
This brick isn't
supposed to be here at all.
How do you know
it's not supposed to be here?
It just isn't.
Hmm...well,
I suppose someone
could trip over
these loose bricks.
Exactly! And someone could trip
over that loose house!
If we each take a side,
we can do this in no time!
Maybe we shouldn't all split up.
[ Imitates rimshot ]
I was thinking
about buying shoes.
Hmm.
We all want
the tennis ball thrown,
but we never want to drop it.
Drop it!
I do enjoy the occasional leaf
of romaine lettuce myself --
just don't tell
the missus.
This hole in the ground
provides an interesting look.
Our mail delivery service
is built around them.
It's fast, and everybody
gets something.
No disappointed faces for
empty mailboxes in this kingdom.
Okay. Okay. Stop pushing.
I'm going. I'm going.
So, what about
your missing walls?
You mean
the open quarter?
Do your houses have walls
on all sides?
How do your people get
fresh air, or dry their clothes?
Hmm. You put a lot of thought
into your designs.
This is
just how it is.
Huh?
Hmm.
Bleh!
Phew!
Ha. Take that,
Miss Carlson!
Now who needs improvement
in cleaning up after herself
and cursive and brevity?
Huh?
Aah!
Do not remove the orbs.
Got it.
I'll write that down
with less jammy hands.
Hmm.
We should probably
get going anyway.
Atticus?!
One-One?!
I guess neither of them know
how long an hour is.
What's going on?
Someone has moved the jam.
It's dried up!
Well, yeah, I was trying to
help you clean it up.
Whoa!
How are we supposed to slide
to the other side?
Everything is going to be
slowed down if we have to walk!
Oh, you...use this?
I-I didn't even think --
Hey, Chief,
I'm gonna be late.
No. No. No.
jam pond has been dried up.
No, I don't know
why it happened.
I know how it happened, but
I don't know why it happened.
I'm really sorry.
Oh, no.
Where's One-One?
Atticus?!
Atticus, what's going on?
Have you seen One-One?
Seen him?
We're trying to stop him,
but we can't reach!
If he moves all those stairs,
the gravity will go with them,
and our kingdom
will be torn apart!
One-One.
Uhh...
Aah!
Whoa!
One-One,
you have to stop!
What are you doing?!
I'm helping,
Miss Tulip. I'm putting it...
...where it's supposed to be.
If they knew it was broken...
...they would have fixed it.
They don't need
to worry anymore.
I'm here to get things
back in order.
One-One,
you're really scaring me.
Yeah. Yeah.
Now I'm floating away!
Why are you
doing this?!
I have to help
put things in order.
It wouldn't be like this
if I had just been better.
Look around you.
This isn't helping.
How can I not try and fix it?
It's my fault.
Is that what you think?
That it's your fault?
I know it.
No, One-One.
It's not your fault
the car is this way.
There isn't a fault,
it just is.
But all this, you trying to
make it your responsibility...
this is causing
real harm.
Don't you see?
I know what it's like
to think that if you had
just been better,
things would've been different,
that you're responsible
for fixing things that are
beyond your control.
Just know that I speak
from experience when I say
this is not your fault.
And I still want to help you,
One-One, if you'll let me.
Whoa!
Hey!
Your Highness, we both
feel terrible, don't we?
Sorry.
He's kind of going through
a lot right now.
Well, the whole sky's gone.
Yeah, it's missing.
But there's
a different sky behind it.
Oh, the whole portfolio's
going to be delayed.
Well, this is
quite the mess.
If I may, the Corginian
Response Team
specializes
in disaster relief.
Well, they mostly work
with doorbell aftermath,
but I still think
they could be of help.
I may take you up
on that offer, my friend.
Hello! I'm One...
...One.
I know.
I'm Tulip.
Do we ever truly know
who we are?
But
with my best friends by my side,
we push onward --
to our homes and mothers!