Why are there so many cars
where I end up picking stuff out of my hair?
You're telling me.
Here, lemme help.
Hmm.
Nail file.
Tweezers.
Mirror.
Ah!
Okay, hold still.
I trust you.
Success!
Ooh! Me next!
This is my cocoon now.
Hee hee hee hee!
Whoa!
Everything is chrome.
I don't think anything
will stick to our hairs here.
It's like a skating rink, but with mirrors!
It's like a... vain person's skating rink?
Who is that dog
beneath me?!
How has he obtained
the Imperial Crown of Corginia?
Atticus, that's your reflection.
Oh, this is terribly embarrassing.
I—
I just—
Whoo-hoo!
Whoa!
I guess we're dealing
with another locked door
or puzzle, or...
Oh, man, do you guys remember—
Whoa!
No, I don't remember "Whoa!"
My memory has been
terrible ever since The Change.
What change?
My new haircut,
didn't you notice?
No, look!
My reflection isn't moving with me!
Are your reflections broken too?
I'm not broken.
Whoa! You're alive?
Oh no. I'm sorry about all the times
I've picked my nose in front of you.
Not gonna lie,
that was gross.
Do you know why
I can't open the door?
Doors work differently in this car.
I have to be the one to open them
with you as my reflection.
This isn't gonna suck me
into a loop of my own memories, is it?
Nah. We place our foot
on the ground
at the same time
in the opposite direction.
Then we can cross the barrier
into each other's world.
I don't know about
this world-switching business.
Well, if you want to stay
in this car forever, fine by me,
but it's gonna get
real boring, real quick.
Trust me.
Hmm.
Yeah. I can't just stay here.
Okay.
On three.
One,
two,
three!
Whoa!
Tulip! Are you all right?
Yeah, it's just... colder?
Hah.
Ready to open the door?
One,
two,
three!
Wow! Thanks, Mirror Me!
Do we do the same thing
to switch back?
Oh, that's how we switch back.
I didn't say I was going
to switch back.
I haven't come
this far on the train
to get bamboozled
by my own reflection!
Excellent use
of "bamboozled," Old Tulip!
I'm not "Old Tulip!"
"Former Tulip" it is.
You can keep calling her Tulip,
because I'm not her,
and I'm not living
her life anymore.
I don't have to do
your stupid coding anymore.
I don't have to eat
your stupid onions anymore.
I'm gonna explore the world
on my own!
I'm gonna touch a tree,
or, like, smell something!
What's something
that smells good?
Let's see: asphalt,
gasoline, sulfur,
other petroleum-based products...
If my reflection is
a separate person...
Can you guys talk too?
Salutations.
Um, hello. Hi.
No! Not again!
Can you guys get me
back up to my world?
I don't know!
It's basically my first day!
I've only been reflected in a river before,
and he keeps barking at me!
I've already alerted
Reflection Enforcement.
They'll bring her to justice.
You called the flecs on me?!
You little jerk!
You Tulip Prime?
Yes... I think.
Don't arrest me! She said
I had to switch to open the door!
No need to explain.
Slivers'll do anything
to get what they want.
Slivers?
Cracked reflections.
They're called slivers. Get it?
We're gonna have
to go above.
So get the skins...
and the sander.
Whoa! Hey, man!
Do we really need
the sander for this?
You want that little defect
running around in the prime world?
We keep the barrier intact.
You got that?
I got it. I got it.
Put the prime in the van.
Hey! Stop!
Miss Tulip!
What are you doing with her?!
She doesn't wanna
be around for this.
If your reflection doesn't
turn herself in,
we'll find her and we'll polish her
down to a pile of nothing.
A pile of nothing?
You can't kill her!
I-I just thought she'd go
to jail or something!
That shatter, that sliver,
is not a person.
She exists to reflect
your existence,
and if she isn't serving
that purpose,
then we'll make sure
she doesn't exist at all.
Get this prime outta my sight.
Hey!
Lemme out!
Come on, you can't do this!
No, stop!
Tulip!
No!
Hey...
Huh?
The Prime unlocked
the door!
What?
Stay here and keep them distracted!
Stop.
That sliver just doesn't
know all the rules yet.
Suit up.
Remain where you are, gentlemen!
I am a pacifist by nature,
but a warrior by necessity.
I'm a robot!
Stop!
You can't leave me trapped here!
If it means I get to be free...
then I'm doing it.
Hey. I can help you
if you talk to me.
That's funny,
coming from you.
Huh?
Wh-What is that
supposed to mean?
I have to do everything
you do, remember?
You're always in your room
ignoring everyone.
You never ask for help.
I'm not ignoring everyone.
I can just handle
my problems myself!
That's completely different!
Skipping texts from Mikayla?
Pretending you couldn't
hear Mom because,
"Sorry, I was just
so busy making my game!"
Just go away, Tulip!
That's what you do best!
Okay. You're right.
I don't like asking for help
when I have a problem.
I guess I should.
But... that proves you should
be talking to me now!
I don't want those mirror police to hurt you.
Who cares what they do to me?
I can't step outside!
There aren't any reflective
surfaces out there!
I don't even have a name.
I'm still nothing.
I'm nothing at all.
No. You're someone!
If we switch back,
I think I can get you a new mirror.
Bad dog! Bad dog!
Hello, Miss Tulip!
We're melting people!
So, what's new with you?
There goes the sliver!
We gotta go!
You stay here in the prime world,
I'm going after that sliver!
But the Buddy System!
The Buddy System!
Aw, geez!
One-One, my multitool!
Okay! Ready?
Ready!
Now!
You are your own reflection!
Come on!
I'm out.
Okay, time to stand on
your own two feet, please!
Get him off me!
Let's go!
You let a sliver out
into the prime world?!
Get back here!
Huh?
Hmm?
Sorry, everyone!
Oh, man.
Aw, yeah.
This is such a boring car
to see first.
Are you kidding?
This. Is so. Cool!
Do you think they'll let me
open an account?
Will I get a checkbook?
Look! Ah, it's those
little pens on chains!
I used to get so motion sick
when I'd have to reflect in these.
Here.
Now no one can keep you trapped, ever again.
Thanks, Tulip.
Well, I'm glad
I was able to help you.
Now c'mon, we better keep moving.
Nah, hard pass.
I spent my whole existence
living your life.
I'm going my own way now.
Okay.
I don't need this glove.
And you don't, either.
Who cares what the train thinks?
Only you control your life.
Good luck, Tulip Prime.
Good luck, Mirror—
...well, good luck to you,
whoever you turn out to be.