Hmm.
Miss Tulip?
I don’t want to
get cavities, either.
Oh, of course not.
Uh...
Here ya go.
Don’t forget to get
the ones in the back!
You’re not my dentist.
Tulip, hello.
So, with the humidity
in that luau car,
along with the hard floors here,
my fur and I seem to be
having a disagreement.
Well, I think it kinda
suits you, but...
Very regal.
I appreciate it.
My tartar is under control!
I can see that.
All right, you two ready?
Ready!
At your command.
I declare bankruptcy!
Hmm. No exit in sight...
Miss Tulip.
Look at all these mums!
I guess we could just
stand here, not moving,
and give a real hard look,
out here on the floor,
where we won’t be distracted.
Again, without moving.
Or I suppose we could
take a quick break to—
Whee!
Now this is the kinda thing
I’m gonna miss when I get home.
Home?
Weren’t you trying
to get to Oshkosh?
Well, I mean, I was trying
to get to game design camp,
but... it’s over.
Now I just...
kinda wanna go home?
Hmm.
Hey, Atticus?
Thanks for sticking
with me through all this.
A king needs to avenge the wrongs
committed against his kingdom.
Turning a blind eye
to what that monster did
isn’t an option.
But... You don’t need me for that.
I’ve got a lot of stuff going on,
stuff that you don’t
have to deal with.
Tulip, everything
we have dealt with,
we have dealt with as a team.
I have never questioned
our alliance or friendship,
the latter of which
I value more.
Thanks.
You’re a good boy.
I’m a good man.
Heroes! We need heroes!
He could be anywhere.
Oh my jeepers!
Are you three the champions
I’ve been waiting for?
You are in luck.
I am Atticus, King and Uniter
of the Cardigans and the Pembrokes.
Well, I’m Khaki Bottoms.
And all of the cotton
is rushing to my head.
Sorry, Mr. Bottoms.
I’m Tulip, and this is One-One.
My cotton is where
it’s supposed to be.
Look at you three!
This is perfect!
I have an artifact
that needs to be returned
to its sacred holding chamber:
the Jiggle Wiggle.
Rewards await
adventurers who are bold!
Yeah, adventure.
Can’t get enough of it.
Bottoms up!
The first trial
has claimed many.
I can see why.
Hmm.
Miss Tulip, without a helmet?!
I live dangerously.
Oof!
Ta-da!
They’re gonna make
a statue of her one day.
We’re also heroes!
We’ll put that one down
as a team effort.
Let’s keep it up.
Wait!
Bshhh!
Bshhhtzhhht!
Force field.
You’re gonna have to solve
the puzzle to deactivate it.
We could be stranded
up here for weeks.
I’ll split up the rations.
I’ll warn you, I’m gamey.
Fear not, One-One.
I’ve danced this tango
once or twice before.
Hah.
Ooh.
Hmm.
Hmm-hmm!
A bold move.
...Bzzhhhhhhhhhhh...-tch!
Bzzhhhhhhhhhhh-tch!
Okay, it’s safe to go now.
Hup!
After you, champion.
The final test:
the punching bags of pain.
There she goes.
Wow!
Been nice knowing ya.
Yay!
With courage and grace,
a champion rises
to the challenge.
Very cozy.
Oh my jeepers, thank you so much!
I tell you, few eyes get to
gaze upon its majesty.
You are so lucky.
And now the artifact can rest.
And the world
is made whole again!
While heroism of your caliber
can never be properly rewarded,
your bravery
must be recognized.
You may select any of the treasures
Jiggle Wiggle!
An excellent choice!
It’s basically
the most fun thing ever.
Whoa.
Neat.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
We gotta go!
Right now!
How do we get outta here?
Oh, but you just got here!
And the feast of a thousand chicken nuggets—
No. This is serious.
Where’s the exit?
All the way down,
left, then right.
You’ll get to a slide,
and the door is just outside.
You need to hide
someplace safe, Khaki.
Atticus, One-One.
I think that—
Shh.
Tulip, One-One,
it has been an honor,
but now is the time
for you to save yourselves.
No, Atticus.
Stay here.
I didn’t leave my kingdom
on a crusade
only to cower
before my dragon.
Atticus!
Huh?
This would have been
so much easier for all of us
if you had just stayed put.
But instead, you go
through car after car,
interfering with my plans,
attacking my Steward for months.
And despite all of that,
I still wanted to help you.
I send The Cat
to offer you your tape,
to live inside
your happiest memories.
But what do you do
with my gift?
You reject it, and you continue
to march against me.
And now look
where you ended up.
Who... Who are you?
Now that I’ve tracked them
down for you, may I go?
Where’s the robot?
One-One! Run!
Bring the robot to me.
And then I give you
your freedom.
No!
I found them.
That was the deal.
I did my job.
Your job is to follow directions.
And I am directing you.
Aah! One-One!
One-One!
And that leaves you...
all alone.
You killed my friends!
Let’s talk about your friends.
They didn’t have to be here.
Wha...?
They had a place on the train,
and you took them out of it.
You brought them here.
You put them in danger.
They were trying to help me!
They were.
And this is the result.
All of this is your fault.
Aww.
No more tears.
Atticus, no!
You will cease your journey.
Why should I listen to you?
Because I am the Conductor.
Atticus!
Atticus?
Atticus? I...
It’s okay, it’s okay.
Miss Tulip!
One-One!
It’s okay to cry.