Look, Miss Tulip!
I found your shoes,
and now I'm a shoe head!
Who's a shoe head?
Shoe-Head, that's who!
Thanks.
I told you
Boot Body would be funnier.
Wait! Are we leaving
Atticus behind?
He's not Atticus anymore.
Your number's
going up!
You're losing progress,
Miss Tulip.
What progress?
Atticus is gone, and my number's
not gonna change that!
Nothing
will ever change.
I'm stuck
on this train forever.
Fatalism doesn't
suit you, kitten.
After all, you're my favorite
person arbitrarily named
after a particular
kind of flower.
One that bounces back!
Quite right.
Now, as you've
no doubt noticed,
I'm trapped beneath
the weight of...
childhood escapism.
Might I propose one
last bonne affaire?
If you help me—
I help you,
then we're done.
No more trades.
But...
what would you gain?
Now, to hold up
my end of the deal.
I don't ever want to talk
to you again.
But wait!
There's still time
to cure the dog!
Don't you dare
lie to me again!
No lies!
He can be turned back,
and the solution
is in this tape.
Last time I saw
one of these,
I almost got trapped
in my own memories forever.
That's because it was
your own tape.
This one belongs to...
another.
And while it's admittedly
a little voyeuristic,
it's not dangerous.
Oh, sure.
You've only lied to me
twice now.
Why not go for a third?
Yeah! Fool her thrice,
shame on me!
Our goals aren't
wholly dissimilar.
The Conductor
tried to kill me.
Fine.
But you're
watching it first.
Deal.
Ugh.
Took you
long enough.
Luckily, I was in dire
need of a cat nap.
Sleeping's creepy.
Aah! One-One!
How'd you get here?
I followed you.
Yeah, but how?
I 'unno.
So, the glorified wind-up toy
will be joining us.
I am glorious.
So...
what exactly are we looking
for here?
We'll know it
when we see it.
Fine. But if you hated
the Conductor so much,
why'd you help him?
Je suis désolé.
I thought if I found you,
I'd be left alone.
That's funny!
That didn't work
at all!
No.
It didn't.
Excellent work, Alrick.
Perhaps you should spend less
time with your toys, Amelia.
It's not a toy.
It's a crystal radio.
Who's this goof?
Someone
very important.
Ugh!
Mark, I know it was you.
Again!
Ugh!
One-One,
did you do that?
Yeah! I did! Again!
Ball, cease this
foolishness.
Fine-uhhh.
One-One,
how did you do that?
I 'unno.
Wha—
Engineering.
Derived from the Latin words
"ingeniare," to contrive.
This memory better not be
another waste of time.
I can't do this.
There are too many people.
You wanna
make a run for it?
Bunk off before
they hand us diplomas?
Here.
Congratulations, class of '76.
Wait...
is that...?
Quick, in here.
No change
to call a cab, love.
Wait, there's a new trick
I learned.
If we play the right tones
into the receiver,
we can control
the network.
Hello?
Whoa!
It worked!
Hi, y-yes,
we need a taxi.
Tell 'em
we're sopping wet!
Shush.
Shh. Shh. Shh.
No, no, not you.
Yes, you!
We're very dry.
100% dry. Very dry.
This isn't helping.
A-mel-i-a.
The Conductor?
Mm-hmm.
It is I,
your normal boy-friend.
I am a hu-mon.
This is how
I sound now.
I do hope that it's
acceptable.
Oh, very acceptable.
But you're obviously
a robot.
And me?
I'm just a simple hu-mon.
But perhaps we can bridge
the gap
between our two
civilizations.
So...
what do you think?
Oh.
Plato says love
is a serious mental disease.
That, we can
agree upon, ball.
So, this is
the Conductor's tape?
He's just some...
British guy?
What happened
to him?
So impatient.
Just watch.
No! We're done
wasting time!
I want to save
my friend!
Let's blow this joint,
Miss Tulip!
Hey, c'mon.
Please, open up,
Look, I know it's hard,
but it'll be good to go.
We're all here for you.
Uh, where's Amelia?
Gone forever?
Well, the service...
it's starting now.
Wha!
Why can't we reach him?
The tape reflects how
each memory was stored,
and the Conductor keeps
this memory at a distance.
Beaten by the system.
One-One, you rewound
this tape earlier,
and you made us fall.
Can you get us
a better view?
I think so.
Huh?
There!
Take us in.
What the...?
Let's follow him.
Amelia?
Amelia. She's stuck here
like me.
Oui. Once upon
a train,
there was a different
Conductor.
Until Amelia arrived and ousted
them for her own purposes.
How does this
help Atticus?
We're right back
where we started!
Information is power,
kitten.
Notice anything...
important?
Cannons.
Wait, so, uh, the Conductor
repurposed that cannon?
Which means...
I could repurpose it, too.
I-I could use it
to save Atticus!
Ta-da.
You dragged me
through a tape
when you could have just told me
that in the first place?
Oh, I guess I should've just
told you how to save the dog?
Yes, you should have
just told me!
But where's
the showmanship?
Don't you get it?
Seeing her tape
just made things harder!
It was easier when I thought
the Conductor was
some heartless
robot thing.
She turned Atticus
into a monster.
I don't want to feel
bad for her.
But now I know she's a person
named Amelia,
who was in love and...
she's hurt.
And she's running away
from the changes in her life...
...because she's afraid.
Like me.
Home...
Hooray!
Now you'll be
gone forever!
To be clear,
that's a good thing.
No.
I can't leave while Atticus
is still a monster.
But what about
your door?
I'll just have to take it
with me.
If the Conductor
is just a person
and the train
is just a machine,
then what's stopping me
from doing what she did?
I-It's like programming.
W-We're gonna use your shuttle
as a controller.
I saw that the train has
some kind of input socket
next to the door.
How do we connect the shuttle
and the input?
I can help!
Did you just break
my shuttlecraft?
Depends.
Who's asking?
My paws are your paws.
Where to, kitten?
Take us to the engine.