There it is.
The end of the train.
Wrong, kitten.
The beginning of the train.
Ooh, the Engine has a splinter.
Amelia’s building
more train cars?
The train is never finished, kitten.
Do we have to go through
the new car to get in there?
You will have to go
through the new car,
for this where I bid you adieu.
What?
No, stay!
Tut tut. I’ve held up my end
of the bargain.
I gave you a lift for free,
which was very generous of me.
Well, I-I guess...
goodbye...
Cat...?
Uh, is it "Cat"?
The Cat.
Well, thank you
for doing the right thing.
I always do the right thing.
Is Evil Atticus hungry?
He’s not evil!
Eh, nature versus nurture.
Hmm.
Do you think my mum is in there?
I don’t know, buddy.
I want you to stay
in my backpack, okay?
Hey, Amelia!
Loved your movie.
Get out!
You’ll damage the new car!
You’re at zero!
You got your exit.
What are you still doing on the train,
you little monster?
I’m here to make a trade.
I get Atticus back, and you...
get your tape!
Where’s that cannon?
Huh?
Ooh, you found
the monster cannon!
Now we can make more. Give it.
No. We’re here to unmake monsters.
Ugh. Which one will change Atticus back?
None of these are corgis, silly.
Huh?
You insensitive—
How dare you force me
to relive those memories!
Just returning the favor, lady.
If you don’t take your exit now,
I’ll send it so far
down the train,
you’ll die of old age
before you see it again.
I’m not leaving until Atticus
is back to normal.
And I thought you were smart.
Huh?
I’m going after the cannon.
I need you to look for a way
to stop the Steward,
or stop the train,
or... something.
End it all.
Got it.
That’s not what I—ugh!
Unbelievable.
Again with the turtles.
You built that weird car
with the turtles in it!
And this is your college campus.
You’re trying to make a car
of your old life.
Of course I am!
You keep a pipe
in your backpack?
It’s a Donut-Holer!
Looking for a way to stop the Steward
Stop the Steward, stop the Steward
So we can turn Evil Atticus back into a dog!
Ugh, too many syllables.
You can’t just make
whatever car you want.
Why not?
I’m just trying to create a car
with Alrick in it.
What if you could create a car, Tulip?
One where your parents
are still together.
But... then they wouldn’t
be my real parents.
It wouldn’t be my real life.
They weren’t... happy together.
I could make you a car
where they are.
I can make a car that’s exactly
how you want it to be.
Just one big happy family.
You can’t even make a car
without any turtles in it!
Stop!
You’ll destroy everything!
A corgi orb.
I’ve just been trying
to keep One at bay.
One what?
One-One!
Mum.
You foolish girl,
this was never about you!
Well, you made it about me
when you attacked my friends!
Gotcha!
No!
Oh, my.
No dog and no parents?
Who will you lose next?
Upsy daisy.
Whoop!
No!
Atticus!
Tulip!
Hey!
Oh, scratchy scratchy!
Thank you. I was feeling
rather exposed without it.
Hello.
I’d like to introduce you
to my mother.
Isn’t she pretty?
She’s got a real heft to her.
One-One, you’re the real conductor?
You’ve just been trying
to get back to the Engine?
Yeah. It’s a little weird, huh?
You ripped One-One out
of the control panel!
He had all that power and he
refused to make a car for me.
You can’t keep trying
to recreate your old life.
You have to learn
how to live in this one.
Don’t you get it?
I don’t want a life
without Alrick.
There’s a hole in the universe
where Alrick used to be.
Why won’t the train
just let me put him back?
I’m really sorry
about your husband, Amelia.
I don’t know what it’s like
to lose someone you love.
But... I do know that neither of us
can go back to the way things were.
We have to adapt
to the changes in our lives.
It’s the only way
things can get better.
It doesn’t matter.
I’ll be on the train forever.
Numbers don’t just go down.
They also go up.
Y-You can still try to get
your number to zero,
no matter how many
mistakes you’ve made.
What about getting rid
of your exit car?
There’s no coming back from that.
Hello!
Mum and I can fix that.
Wha?
What in the name
of Mustard and Stink Tail is that?
An exit can appear in any car.
It’s just a matter of unlocking one.
And zero is the key!
I’m very uncomfortable
with how much I’ve missed.
I’m not stuck
on the train anymore?
But now I have to leave you two.
I-I wasn’t ready for it
to happen all of a sudden like this.
You, a-and this, and...
and I... it was...
And Atticus, and...
And now...
Me too.
Though my heart is heavy,
I am honored to carry the weight,
for it will remind me of you.
I’ll miss you.
Okay.
Wait, wait.
Hug.
Hug first!
Yay!
C’mere!
Group hug!
Goodbye, Amelia.
I hope you get
your exit someday.
I love you guys.
Tulip! Your dad is here
to pick you up for camp!
Coming!
Hey, Dad!
Hey, you.
Have a great time.
Call me when you get settled in?
I will.
I’ll get her there safe.
So, Bud, you ready?
I’m ready for anything.