Huh?
Welcome aboard,
new passenger!
I'm your conductor, One.-One
I'm your conductor, One-One.
Once you wipe those
groggy little peepers,
you'll probably have
a lot of questions, like:
Where am I?
“Where am I?”
Why am I here?
“Why am I here?”
“Are snacks provided?”
I didn't ask that.
For those of you talking to me
like I'm there in real life,
I'm not!
I'm a cold, steely,
pre-recorded video.
And this is a train
where you sort out your problems.
How about that number
on your hand, huh?
Pretty cool and green.
Every passenger has one.
The numbers are made
by the train based on your life
in order to help you have
the most personalized experience we can offer.
If you want to go home,
get your number down to zero,
and poof, away you go.
I'm a zero.
But always remember there are lots of denizens along the way to help you on your journey.
Don't be afraid to reach out.
Unless the denizen is one of those monsters
with more teeth than body.
Remember,
you can't spell "escape"
without "companionship."
Uh, companion... shape?
Companionscape.
By watching this recording, you've agreed to release the train of any liabilities—
Hey, shiny girl.
Don't be stuck up.
Fresh batch of passenger memory tapes!
Two for one. Today only. Real sad!
Hey, sweetie.
You're shiny.
Lemme take a closer look.
No!
Hello, sliver.
Criminal, halt!
Gotcha.
Huh?
Right there?
Dead end, sliver!
Huh?
Maneuver 406.
Got it, buddy!
Ha!
Leave me alone!
Not until you're ground into dust.
Hey, watch it!
Oop. Sorry!
We can't lose her, not again!
Hm?
Huh?
Why did I hide behind the deer?!
There's no escape, sliver.
We've got you cornered.
And I just love cuttin' corners.
Mm.
Humiliating.
She's gone. Again.
Don't worry, Mace.
We'll get her.
I know that.
Slivers are weak,
think they're above the law.
She made her choice.
But they all get tired,
and they let their guard down...
Think they're safe.
They're never safe.
Well I guess we should get on
through this car, and—
Nope. Your suit is compromised.
Whoops, oh, yeah.
Thanks, buddy.
If this tear gets too big,
I'm a goner.
I'm fully aware.
We'll do one more sweep,
then head back to the station.
Well, on the upside,
the last couple of months tracking her
have been a great,
truly great bonding experience.
Enough.
Yeah, I should shut up.
You got it, buddy.
Phew.
Whoa!
Uh... Thanks for the save.
Well, bye.
Hmm.
Uh, sorry.
I gotta do this alone.
Hey, c'mon! I'm walking!
You go do your thing,
and I'll do mine.
Why are you still here?
You like this stuff, huh?
So... What's your deal?
I hear that.
You from around here?
Huh, glad you asked.
Nope, I'm not.
I'm from a place called
"The Chrome Car."
Well, that's what Tulip,
my prime, called it.
It's actually called the mirror world.
Yeah, don't go there, it sucks.
That's where those flecs are from.
I hate those guys.
They've been chasing me just 'cause I don't wanna
live the rest of my life as somebody's ref—
Okay, this one
or this one?
You... don't care, do you?
Okay, let's not do that.
Nice.
What other colors can you—
Huh, okay. Brown again.
You've got a nice home.
Aww!
Whuzuh?
Deer?
Hey, c'mon, where'd you go?
Deer? Deer?
Deer?
Aw, yeah. Lookin' good...
Okay. Now, just don't move...
Hey, leave him alone.
Whoa.
Hi. I'm Jesse. What's your name?
I don't care who you are.
Why are you putting
sunglasses on a deer?!
Because it's funny.
Look at him!
Look at you...
Aw, come on!
Those are mine!
Some of the cars here
are really bright.
He didn't ask for glasses.
He's just livin' his life.
But he's my deer.
We've been hanging out
for a whole hour,
maybe even a little more.
He's free. He's his own deer.
But if he was anyone's deer,
he'd be my deer,
because I hung out
with him longer, like two days.
Are you sure?
I got all these pics with him.
Pfff! That could be any deer.
This deer can change color.
Oh, well, this guy
doesn't change colors.
He's got laser eyes.
Bzzt! Bzzt!
Seriously? Laser eyes?
Yeah. Well, laser vision.
Heat vision. What do...
What do you call it?
What kind of idiot
do you think I am?
This deer doesn't have—
Does your deer do that?
No?
I think we've been hanging out
with the same deer.
Have you been getting two dinners?
Oh, he's friends with both of us!
Now we're friends, too! By association!
We're travel friends!
What? No.
Travel friends, brought together
by the sheer majesty
of an incredible superpowered deer and—
No.
This deer and I are leaving.
Goodbye, and enjoy putting
sunglasses on random animals.
Dracula's not random.
He's my friend.
Dracula?
You cannot name a deer Dracula.
Let's ask the deer.
Hey, deer. What do you
want to be called?
Dracula.
See? Dracula.
No.
Hmm, yeah.
I guess you're right.
Maybe we should go with something
everyone would be into.
What's everyone's
favorite name?
Oh, Alan! It's Alan.
Wait.
That's it: Alan Dracula!
Let's try it out.
Hello. Have you met
my deer, Alan Dracula?
Oh yeah, sounds like
something I'd say.
Good idea, chrome girl.
No!
That's not his name,
and that's not my name!
You can't go around deciding names
for people without asking.
It's their choice to—
Alan Dracula!
No!