No!
Alan Dracula!
Wow, we're on top
of a tree.
Oh, hey.
If you hadn't distracted me
with that ridiculous name,
I would have noticed
he walked away.
And it's too late
to change it.
I already put him in my phone
as Alan Dracula.
See?
Oh, right.
He's still in here
just as Dracula.
I'm not
dealing with this.
He could be hurt.
Wow. Do you have, like,
special metal strength?
No. I just don't feel pain like
you with your squishy flesh.
Uh, yeah,
I am pretty squishy
and, like, really good
at feeling pain.
If I fall, I'm going to feel
a ton of it.
Fine! Bye!
Oh, man.
Hey, wait up.
Wow.
Ah.
Uh, chrome girl?
I'm not answering
to that.
Sorry.
Uh, what is your name?
You won't know me long enough
for it to matter.
Do I hear some passers-by?
Why, hello, there.
Who might you
and your metal friend be?
Hi.
I'm Jesse.
Well?
You can call me MT.
Hey, how come
they get to—
Have you seen a deer
falling through here?
Hmm, can't say
that I have,
but it's a right pleasure
to meet you two.
I'm Great-Great-Great-Great-
Great-Great-Great-Grandpa
Wilbur Gillicutty.
And this here is
Great-Great-Great-Great-
Great-Great-Great
Grandma
Sinesta Gillicutty.
You can call me
G.G.G.G.G.G.G.S. for short.
And you kids are standing on the
mighty Gillicutty family tree.
This ain't no stinking
Gillicutty family tree!
This is the Trundleshank
family tree. Ptooey.
The Trundleshanks are angry
'cause one of our descendants
married one of theirs
about 100 years ago,
and now they have to live
in our family tree.
Hey, maybe the Trundleshanks
have seen Alan Dracula.
Mr. and Mrs. Trundle?
Oh, no, you don't.
As long you're
on our tree,
you ain't allowed to talk
to no boneheaded Trundleshanks.
I'll talk
to whoever I want.
Hey, I know.
You could name the tree
after both your families,
like my friend Troy.
He took both his parents'
last names.
So instead of being Troy Banks,
now he's Troy Snooterly-Banks.
No way. No how.
Ptooey!
Fine, I don't need
your help anyway.
And Snooterly-Banks?
No wonder you thought
Alan Dracula was a good name.
You shouldn't have left
like that.
Now they're mad at us.
They were being
totally unfair.
But maybe they could help us
find Alan Dracula.
If we could get them
to stop fighting—
They've been fighting
for 100 years.
Well, I bet I could help.
I'm friends with every kind
of group at school—
jocks, theater kids,
eraser kids.
Eraser kids?
The kids who collect their
eraser shavings during the day
and compare them
in the parking lot after school.
I didn't say it was
a common group.
I-I just said I'm able
to be friends with them.
Wow, fitting in,
what a gift.
It's not like that.
It just means I'm likable.
Except to you,
I guess.
Why are you
so mad at me?
Look, it has nothing
to do with you.
It's just...
Okay.
So I used to have this friend
named Tulip,
and we did everything together,
but as we grew up,
I didn't have much
in common with her anymore,
but, um, my parents thought
Tulip was perfect
and wanted me to be
exactly like her,
so I had to stop hanging out
with her so I could be free.
Why would you do that
to your friend?
That's—That's crazy.
Ugh!
This is why I like
hanging out with the deer.
He doesn't tell me
how I should act.
Plus,
he has cool powers,
unlike you, who only has
the power to annoy me.
If you want to get
to Alan Dracula faster,
we should talk to the families
and do what they say.
Then leave me alone
and go do that.
I never asked you
to follow me.
Okay, fine.
I will.
Watch.
I'll form a truce.
It'll be a piece of cake...
or pie.
Some people
don't like cake.
So...
The whole tree
is buzzing about you.
Way to stick it
to those awful Gillicuttys.
I wasn't trying
to stick it to anyone.
I'm just looking
for my friend.
He's a deer.
He's about deer height.
W-W-What was the look
on Wilbur's face
when you told him you
didn't trust the Gillicuttys?
I didn't say that.
Oh, you know what?
I bet you have a lot more in
common with them than you think.
In elementary school,
we learned this song
that I think
might be helpful.
It's called "When I Look at
You, I See Me," and it goes—
Is it true
you spit in his face?
No!
Hi, there, little girl.
Going down the tree?
Yep.
You shouldn't
talk to her, little girl.
She's as dumb
as they come.
Can it, ding-dong.
Aw, this from a woman who choked
to death eating an orange peel.
I told you, it's the most
fibrous part of the fruit.
You died because you sat
on a toilet seat too hard.
Have either of you
seen a deer?
No, I ain't.
You?
Mnh-mnh.
Ugh, didn't think so.
See you later.
Sorry you both died
in such embarrassing ways.
Hmm. So Mr. and
Mrs. Trundleshank are mad
'cause you Gillicutty
quadruplets
broke their milk bottles
every morning.
Think you could apologize?
No. They never invited us
to their kids' birthday parties.
Mm, yeah.
I mean, that's tough on a kid.
We couldn't afford to feed every
child in town at our parties.
Yeah, that's a valid point, too,
affordability.
But we were the only kids
who weren't invited.
Yeah, you shouldn't
leave people out.
That's— That's true.
Hey, whose side
are you on?
None of us are helping you
get down this tree
until you pick a side.
Um, I-I don't—
I don't want anybody to get mad at me.
Choose!
How about we all try singing
this great song together?
It's called "When I Look at You,
I See Me."
Get off our branch.
Ah, great.
Oh, hi.
How was your
popularity contest?
Well, trying to make everyone
happy didn't really work out.
Looks like your punching
isn't doing much good, either.
You probably
slowed me down too much.
If I'd gotten down here
sooner,
the branches wouldn't
be this bad.
You don't know that.
Yeah?
Well, you don't know anything
and can't help anyone.
You can't even
help yourself.
That's why passengers get on
this train in the first place.
Hey, don't pu—
Great, now the tree's
gonna eat us.
Why are you acting like
I'm some kind of—
Jesse!
No.
I was yelling.
It's still my turn to yell.
No, Jesse, your hands.
Ah, it's changing me.
Aah!
Help!
Man, I don't want
to be made out of wood.
Everybody at school
will call me Pinocchio.
They won't call you that.
Okay, they'll probably
call you that
if you ever
get back to school.
Why'd you have to
say that?
Sorry.
It's okay.
Wait, Jesse.
They moved a little.
You don't have to
lie to me.
Jesse, really.
When I become a tree, I want you
to move on with your life,
find Alan Dracula,
be happy.
And please know
I don't blame you.
Maybe this was fate.
Fated to be a tree boy.
Ow!
Why did you—
Ah, I'm not a tree boy.
What happened?
I kept my eyes open
during the scary parts.
Oh, wow.
Hmm.
Ahh!
You're a terrible tree.
Hey.
It's doing its best.
Just kidding.
You're a beautiful tree.
That's what's happening.
Fighting makes
the branches grow.
Pray, good sir, wouldst thou
care to follow me
down to the bottom
of this noble tree?
Oh, uh, I'd love to.
Good, keep going.
Thank you for your
very generous offer.
Lovely day, isn't it?
Yes, verily.
I like how your hair
is made of needles.
My compliments to the chef.
Mwah!
And I like your hair.
It's brown,
how original.
Shall I sing a song?
I'd absolutely love it.
When I look at you
Your metal skin is very shiny,
like a car
that was just washed by,
uh, like, a sunbeam
and just, like,
super shiny.
Hey, deer!
Where are you?
Alan Dracula!
Bleat once if you're okay,
twice if you're hurt.
Alan Dracula!
Deer!
Unbelievable!
Alan, A-Drac,
Alan Dracula!
Hey, deer!
So look.
I guess I shouldn't have
yelled at you so much,
but only because it made
this stupid tree grow.
Me too.
Sorry.
I still want to be on my own
with the deer,
but technically
we are both his friend.
Not us,
we're not friends.
But we're friends
with him separately,
so here's the only solution
I can think of.
I'll travel with you and
help you get your number down.
Really?
But only because then you'll get off the train
and I'll get to stay with,
for lack of a better name,
Alan Dracula.
Yes!
Sorry.
Okay,
so let's do this.
What's your number at?
32.
Psh! I'll get you home
in no time.
What was it when you
got on the train?
31.
Your number
has gone up?
Ow!
I don't know if you know
how much metal hurts.
I'm soft, squishy.
You're hard and mean!