I've seen this number
thing before
so I'm basically
totally an expert.
You're gonna have to listen
to everything I say
if you want to get home.
All you need to do
is learn stuff about yourself.
Maybe you should
be taking notes.
Got a pen
and some paper.
Oh, I have my receipt
from Gas and Dog.
See, my brother Nate and I
have this deal
where we always go halfsies
on the Zesty Nacho Supreme...
Ugh, never mind.
Wait a second.
You should be doing this.
Open the door.
Learn something.
You're the boss.
♪♪
This is so cool.
[ Wind rustles ]
Whoa.
Jesse?
Aah!
Oh. Hello.
Bleh.
There you go.
Marcel is gonna
hook you up.
And you are Marcel?
Oh, yes.
Check it out.
[ Chuckles ]
That's me.
Hey! Are you
learning lessons?!
I learned his name
is Marcel.
Does that count?Did your number go down?
No!Then it doesn't count!
Keep learning!
Well, there's a lot
to learn here.
We just started.
I haven't had an explorer
in ages.
As you can see, there's a lot
of unmapped territory.
And that map
I gave you.
The one you spit
from your mouth?
Yeah. That's the one.
It's been torn to bits.
But if you find
the pieces,
everything else will open up
for you -- for me -- us.
So, this is great, huh?
Yeah.
It's pretty good.
MT: So, are you just gonna
keep him now, or what?
Because I kind of just want
to hang out with his deer.
Oh. I'm sorry.
Here you go.
Alright.
Let's see this thing.
Hey, jerk!
What's the deal with
your electric map?
I'm so sorry, but there can
only be one explorer.
I don't make the rules.
You can tag along
if you'd like.
It's pretty fun.Whatever.
Maybe you need to carry more
stuff to get your number down?
Yeah. maybe.
Just show me the map.
Hmm.
Oh. Well, this seems
pretty straightforward.
A little too
straightforward.
The X seems right,
but a dotted line?
Like following a line is
gonna get your number down.
How about those?
You want me to walk
on the mountains?
Definitely.
You'll get some balance in,
overcome some hardships.
Can't get that
on a dotted line.
♪♪
So, Marcel, are you just gonna
watch us the whole time?
Yep. Pretty much.
How am I doing?I like what I'm seeing so far.
Yes.
Huh?
H-hey, there's a piece
of map up here.
MT: Bring it here.
Can I take the dotted line
this time?
Mmm, I guess.
But on your way back,
think about your shortcomings,
and how you deal with them.
You got it.
Okay. Let's put
this map together.
Eh, you do it.
♪♪
Not too bad.
But what we're really
focused on...
Up again?
Is this thing
working right?
Your hand
is trash.
You've got to learn
more stuff.
It's just weird that
your number keeps going up.
Tell me what
your problems are.
Hmm. Oh, well,
one time during lunch,
my friend said
they didn't like celery,
but I kind of like celery,
so they gave me their celery.
And then, the lunch lady saw,
and thought I was
wasting celery,
so she stood there,
and made me eat, like,
30 pieces of celery.
That sounds more like a problem
the lunch lady needs fixed.
[ Gasps ] Do you think
Mrs. Graham is on the train?
Yeah. Probably. But Mrs. Graham
isn't here right now,
trying to hang out
with my deer.
Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey.
Phone time is not
gonna fix you.
This is number time.
[ Rustling ]Huh?
Huh?
And now, look at that.
That could be you
chewing that map,
and your number
could've dropped by 10.
Give, give it,
give it, give it.
It's covered in
Allen Dracula spit.
Is that alright?
I mean, the map had
my spit on it,
and it's still good,
right?
It's better than good.
Ah, water!
Are you okay?
Non-reflective.
Paper water.
Ha. I was just surprised
that it wasn't real water,
and it's not reflective, or wet,
or shiny, or something.
That's weird, right?
That's surprising.
That's -- Well, off
to the mermaids.
So, anyway,
I'm metal.
Huh?
♪♪
Hi. I'm Jesse.
Uh, share your feelings
with them.
Uh, go to game design camp?
I don't know.
So, they had this.
Also, they said
your hair was cool.
Hi. See you.
Thanks.
Okay.
Put the piece in.
More ocean?
There should be a door
piece soon, right?
Oh. Of course.
It's just bad luck on the order
you found those pieces, huh?
But you're so close.
You haven't even
set sail yet.
That's where
the real fun is, eh? Eh?
I guess we don't
have much choice.
That's the spirit --
well, it's not
the best spirit,
but, ah, there's at least
something there.
♪♪
So, you just jumped
right in back there.
What was that about?I'm on the swim team.
It's kind of what I do.
And they tell you to flail
wildly with both arms?
Excuse me?
It's called the butterfly --
which I happen to be
qualified in for State.
You picked the biggest,
stupidest-looking stroke
to be your favorite?
I wouldn't say favorite.
When I started,
we only had one senior
on the team
who swam the butterfly,
and I was the only new guy
who could kind of do it.
The team obviously agreed
I had to do it, so I did.
So, they all agreed
that you should go to State
for something
you don't like?
Well, I didn't actually
go to State.
Too many people qualified,
so they needed someone
to stay behind.
I really, really wanted to go,
but I didn't.
But don't you care about
doing what you want to do?
Yeah. I guess.
I don't know.
I'd love to swim
freestyle sometime.
Nate once asked why
I like it so much.
I think it's because
there's something,
I don't know, just something
about how simple it is.
But they told me if I qualify
for butterfly again next year,
then, maybe, I wouldn't
have to give up my spot,
so it's fine.
Okay.
Kind of sounds stupid
when I say it out loud.
Hmm.
Hey! Alright!
It's not much,
but at this rate,
we'll get you out of here
in no time.
I guess you need to talk more
about sports or something.
Yeah.
That makes sense.
I think we got all we
can get from this car.
Hey, wind guy, it's been fun,
but we're done here.
Let's wrap things
up, huh?
Huh?
I said we're done!
Weren't we just here?
Yeah.
We totally were.
Hey, Marci,
we've already been here!
What's going on?
Uh...
Hello?
Are you just gonna keep us
going in circles forever?
Hey, creep,
I'm talking to you!
You don't know anything!
I'm nice! I'm fun!
I'm helping!
We don't have to stop.
You're trapping us
in this car!
How can you
be trapped?
We can keep exploring,
and expanding the map forever.
The world is as big
as we can make it,
so let's keep making it.
One person guides.
One person follows.
It's a system.
It's great.
Let it be great.
♪♪
What do we do, M.T.?
I...
I don't know.
If I jump in the water,
I'll sink.
Okay. M.T. doesn't
have any ideas.
What can I do?
He doesn't want
the map completed.
We don't have any paper
for the rest of the map.
M.T., I need paper!
I don't have any.
Gas and Dogs Zesty Nacho Supreme
deal receipt.
Oh, no.
Ah.
♪♪
Oh, no.
I'm the wind!
[ Both sigh ]
Heh. That was
pretty good.
Wow. You saved...
Uh, you saved
Allen Dracula.
He says,
"Thank you."
Thanks A.D. I...
Still doing that, huh?
Wow.
This place is pretty nice.
Hmm.
Ah.
Oh, no.
Freeze, sliver.
There's no
running anymore.
[ Both gasp ]
♪♪