Step away from
that criminal!
Criminal?
We got to leave!
Ugh. Come on!
Don't litter, MT!
We're already criminals!
Run!
There's no escape,
sliver!
What?
MT, what is going on?
Later!
Open the door!
Ugh, come on.
You're making
a big mistake, son!
You're harboring
a criminal reflection!
Wait.
Are you the criminal?
No! I- I mean,
it's complicated!
I know you can hear me
in there, sliver.
Ah!
Hey. You okay
in there, son?
What's your name?
Jesse.
Ugh.
Nice to meet you,
Jesse!
I'm Sieve.
I'm a Mirror Officer
of the Peace.
Jesse, do you know
who she is?
She's a dangerous extremist
from our Mirror World.
She'll say anything to get
what she wants.
She did it to her Prime,
and she'll do it to you, too.
Her Prime?
Aw, boy.
She hasn't told you anything,
has she?
Ignore them.
Why?
They've told me more about you
than you have!
I don't owe you
an explanation.
Oh, really?
Where did you get that?
Does it matter?
It's you.
You're a criminal!
Well, you're an idiot!
Yeah, I am,
for trusting you!
I'm going back to the station
for The Lawbreaker.
Mm-hmm.
You're lucky
you ran into me!
Yeah, bad lucky!
Please don't kick me.
Why would we
kick you?
Well, ma'am, the only way
to open the doors
and get out of this here car
is if'n you kick me.
But please don't kick me.
Sorry, but if it's
the only way...
Ugh!
Oh!
You would.
What's that
supposed to mean?
Kicking
a defenseless frog?
Uh, toad.
Sorry.
Kicking
a defenseless toad?
A-thank you very much.
That proves
you're a criminal.
I am not a criminal.
Oh me, oh my! All this anger
and arguin'.
I know where this leads—
to kickin' poor
ol' chub-a-lubby me!
Fine! You don't want me
to kick him?
Then I won't.
Oh, thank my lucky warts.
You can do it because all
you've done is hold us back.
That's not true.
I got us out of
that Map Car!
Yeah, and how long did
that take?
Do you even want
to get off this train?
Yes, of course, I do!
Then kick the toad!
Oh, no,
back to this again.
Oh, oh, please
don't kick me!
Uh, I'm sorry.
Huh?
Uh.
Huh.
Wait a minute.
Just do it already!
Get it over with!
Waiting's the hardest part.
I...think you
have to do it.
Mnh-mnh.
Your number was changing.
Clearly,
it's a passenger thing.
Y'all need anything?
Maybe some cookies
and warm pond water?
Uh, no thanks.
Okay, good.
I-I ran out years ago.
Makes hosting folks
quite difficult.
Hmm.
No, that looks stupid.
Record it!
Jesse, record it!
Man test! Man test!
Man test!
I-I don't know.
If I do it,
can I hang out with you?
Hey, be a man.
Yeah, come on.
Make him do it,
Jesse!
Yeah, it's fine,
just do it already, Nate!
If you don't do it,
you can't be a man!
O-Okay.
Can we do it
on the count of three?
I just don't
want to fall.
Yeah. One...
Aah!
Two, three.
Epic fail!
It-It really hurts.
"It weally hurts."
You failed!
Ah!
Jesse, tell him
he failed!
Nate, you failed
the man test!
Jesse...
Is he crying?
You better not tell Mom!
Did you get all that?
It was epic!
Your brother
beefed it.
What you watching?
Nothing.
Didn't sound like
nothing.
Hey, Jesse, you there?
Y-Yeah, I'm here.
That's great.
I'm so glad you're safe.
You are?
We're not
the bad guys, son.
Look around.
You're the hostage.
We're trying to
save you.
Now, was that
a phone I heard?
Y-Yeah.
Hmm, why isn't it
reflective?
It's really dark
in here right now.
Got you.
Well, you can really help us
out here, Jesse.
All you have do is leave
that phone out till morning,
so we can pop through
the screen reflection
and arrest MT
for her crimes.
Now, I know it's hard,
but she broke the law.
Hmm.
You won't hurt her,
will you?
If she means
that much to you, Jesse,
I suppose we can
make an exception.
Ah!
No!
Jesse, what's happening
in there?
Nice try!
The phone's gone,
flec!
Ah!
Move.
Now, we're gonna do it
my way.
How could you do that?
I wasn't gonna let them in!
Why should I trust somebody
who sells out his own brother?
What?
No, I-I didn't...
It's more complicated
than that.
My friends,
it w-was their idea.
I just thought it would
be funny, I...
But...I didn't mean
to hurt Nate.
Yeah, well, ugh,
he's probably fine.
I wouldn't know.
I didn't get to talk to him
before...here.
Your friends are bad.
You know that,
right?
Maybe.
Ugh!
I probably should've told you
what was going on earlier.
It's true
what those flecs said.
Technically,
I am a "criminal,"
but I didn't do
anything wrong.
So you are a reflection?
Who are you
a reflection of?
Remember that friend
I told you about, Tulip?
I used to reflect her, but I
wanted to live my own life,
make my own memories,
but that's against Mirror Law,
and those flecs have been
chasing me ever since.
So your name, MT, does it stand
for Mirror Tulip?
It's not my name.
I'm just letting you
call me that.
Sorry for breaking
and spray-painting your phone.
It's just the flecs
can show up in any reflection.
I'm never safe.
But your body
is reflective.
Can't they jump
out of you?
Ow!
People can't
jump out of people.
Come on.
That's stupid.
Oh, yeah.
That's stupid,
But the rest of it
is normal.
Sorry, Jesse.
Should've helped us
when you had the chance!
We got to get you out
of here, MT!
Kick me!
Please, kick me!
Wait, now you want
to get kicked!
If all my time in this car
has taught me one thing,
the toad
always gets kicked.
It's the only truth I know.
Kick me!
Kick me straight
in the Gracelands!
But your number
will go up!
Who cares?
We got to go!
Let's just do it
together!
One, two...
Well, now, don't get
too excited, now.
It's... it's still my body
we're injuring.
Whoa!
Huh?
Whoa, baby.
Can't kick
what isn't there!
Gah!
This isn't over,
sliver!
I won't stop until— until...
We'll get her,
buddy.
Yeah!
Whoo!
Huh?
Thank you kindly
for saving me
from an existentially
nightmarish existence.
I won't soon forget it.
Good-byeeeee.
Uh...
Huh.
Jesse, your hand.
Wow, down to 14!
Thank you.