Oh, do you know
my reflection?
We don't all
know each other.
But if you did...
We don't.
Ah, Alan Dracula!
Alan, what is
with you today?
What's with him
every day?
-Wow.
-Whoa.
Do reflections
go to the bathroom?
Okay!
Question time's over.
All right.
All right. All right.
Then what about
singing time?!
Travel friends
They're friends
to the very end
Travel friends
There's no rhythm
in this song
Which makes it
very, very dumb
Easy
Brought together
by the majesty
Of a superpowered deer
Take it, A.D.!
Ah!
Alan Dracula!
Ah! Cold feet! Ooh!
Cold, cold, cold, cold!
Oh, poor little
superpowered deer.
Don't sniff those, okay?
Let's say
your prime dies.
Tulip's gone—
got in a bad Jet-Ski accident
or was eaten by a seal
or something.
Do you reflect her body?
Mm. No.
Once a prime dies,
the flecs make you choose
if you want to have
your memories erased
and reflect a new prime,
or keep your memories
but become a flec to "protect
and enforce the barrier."
But you're not doing
either.
No, both options
are stupid.
Hmm. Yeah, so,
um, if someone—
not me— practices
kissing in a mirror,
can their reflection
see them doing it?
A-Again, not me.
Someone else,
different person.
Did I say "not me"?
Hm? Ew.
Aw, ugh.
Looks pretty deep.
Think Alan Dracula
would let us ride him across?
Huh?
Ohhhhh!
Come on, Casanova!
Hey!
I said it was someone else!
Coming in for a landing,
Alan Dracula!
Ugh!
Aah!
Thanks.
Much appreciated.
Ah! Is it too much to ask
for a regular door?
Alan Dracula,
be useful for once
and laser away
those vines.
Watch— they'll just
explode into more mud.
Oh!
That's more like it,
Alan Dracula!
Hey, wow.
Thank you.
I think you guys
are pretty good, too.
-Whoa!
-You can talk?
-You can talk!
Well, um, yeah,
you bet.
Another one of my amazing
superpowers, I guess,
or magic or science.
You know,
one of those things.
Yeah, yeah, checks out.
No, it doesn't.
Hey, what's in your mouth.
Hello, hi.
Nice to meet you.
Hopped aboard your deer pal
back in the mud.
Out of the mouth,
parasite, now!
Hey! What's with
the name-calling?Whoa!
You want to call me a name,
how about Perry?
You'd like that,
right, Perry?
That's cute.
I'm cute.
Saying you're cute
doesn't make you cute.
Yeah, parasite!
Pals, that's such
a harsh label.
I'm a symbiotic creature.
I help and hang out
like those little birds
who clean crocodile teeth.
You don't call them
parasites.
And, hey,
check this out.
I'm practical.
Remember when I zapped away
those vines?
Your deer pal Alvin would
have never done that.
I'll never sneeze your feet
into ice,
and you can ride me
like a horsey all day long.
Convenient, right?
But I thought you came
from the mud.
How do you know
about all that?
I can read this guy's mind,
and let me tell you --
he likes you both
very much...
...almost as much as grass,
which seems to occupy
every other waking thought.
That actually checks out.
So Alan can still
think for himself?
Oh, sure, old antler-head
loves this new setup.
We're like
brain roommates.
MT, having an Alan Dracula
who actually listens to us
might not be
such a bad thing.
As long as it's not
hurting him.
Oh, wow, gosh.
I would never.
Whoa!
-Ah!
Whoa.
Now let's get this boy's
number down.
-Uh...
After you.
See, that's polite.
I'm polite.
Please never turn your hoof
into an adult human hand again.
Down low, APD!
Anyone else feel
a song coming on?Whoa!
Travel friends
They once were three
but now they're four
The travel friends
are so much more
Let's bring it home,
Jesse.
Travel frieeeends
Ah!
Hey, M...
Hey.
I know this is weird,
but maybe we can give
Perry a shot.
I don't trust him.
Yeah, well, you didn't trust me
at first, either,
but look at us now.
Yeah.
Tardy friends
Bow-bow-ba-bow
They're tardy
till the very end
Hey, does Alan seem
bigger to you?
Hmm. Maybe?
No way am I bigger.
We're outside, and I just look
bigger because of the big train.
That's now how
perspective works.
Sure, it is.
-Aw!
-Stop doing that.
But you said
no adult hands.
Ahh!
Baby hands are worse.
Put that away.
Ugh!
Ah, baby hands.
The judges are
getting restless!
And you are?
I'm Sashay, baby.
I'm head honchess here
at Sashay's Runway Fairway.
If you don't hit
the exit runway pronto,
the judges
are going to wig out.
Pun very much intended.
Exit runway?
Yes, darling.
The only way out of here
is to dress to impress
with finesse.
Oh, and do this.
Ta-da!
-Uh...
Seems easy enough.
Tut-tut! We can't keep
those judges waiting.
It's time for
Sashay's Runway Fairway.
Give it up for
our first contestant.
You won't believe
what you'll Jes-see!
Judges?
Lucky number 9,
looking fine.
Round that up to a 10,
and you're a winner, darling.
You may exit.
Hope you didn't fill up
because this tank's
running on MT!
Avant-garde?
More like avant-great!
You may exit.
Don't stake our final contestant
in the heart
before he steals yours.
It's Alan Dracula!
Heh.
Heh, heh.
-Oh, oh, oh!
-Whoa.
Hole in 1 million, baby!
I couldn't have done it
better myself.
You may all exit!
Whoa. I can't believe
I'm saying this,
but nice work in there.
Hey, hey, hey! How about
a little personal space?
But I thought
Alan Dracula liked that.
Well, you know,
people change.
Hey, check out
this new door.
Look, ma, no baby hands.
Who's hungry for adventure?
Me! I'm also hungry
for real food!
Complimentary chips and—
hey! —thick, meaty chili.
Meat and chips -- great!
I'll bet you the old Alden
couldn't do that. Ha, ha!
Ah!
Mmm. Oh.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Alan Dracula is
a vegetarian!
Well, not anymore.
See, I'm growing and changing,
just like you, Jerome.
Um, it's Jesse.
Yeah, like I said,
Jess—
Why are his powers
going haywire?
I think Alan Dracula's
trying to kick Perry out.
Alan's fighting it off
like an infection,
and you're definitely
getting bigger.
Uh, okay, rude.
I'm pretty sure
I'm the same size!
Ahhh!
Ugh! Ugh! Ugh!
Alan doesn't want this!
You have to let him go!
But you'll be stuck with a deer
who doesn't listen to you.
We don't like him
because he listens.
We like him because
he's Alan Dracula!
Whoa!Okay, so maybe we both
want the same thing --
me out of Amblin Dunkula,
but maybe I'm
a little stuck here, guys.
I could use some help.
How fast can you get
to that flower car?
Help me, Jiles and MD!
Oh, boy!
Hey, strong hands.
You work out?
Jesse, here!
Mnh!
Ha!
Ah— ah— achoo!
Aaaaah! Oof.
Ow. Ooh.
Hm. Aah!
Welcome back,
Alan Dracula.
Sorry we didn't
get you out sooner.
Huh?
Look at that— Alan Dracula
got your number down.
Wow!
Great job, Jimmy.
Kind of thanks to me, too,
though, right?
Now, whose mouth
am I hopping in next?
Guys, guys!
Aw, come on!
I spent two years stuck
in a succulent.
Let me hop in one of
your mouths!