Hi. I'm Jesse.
It's not alive, ding-dong.
We don't know that.
Eh, fair point.
C'mon.
Huh?
Oh, look what I got here!
Hey, look what I got.
Nice!
My family goes to powwow
at our county fair every year.
One time, Nate wrapped his whole
head in cotton candy and—
Hey, you'll make things right
with him when you get home.
Yeah. Totally.
Tulip went to the carnival
every year too.
The only part I ever got to experience
was the house of mirrors,
but with the flec situation,
let's not tempt fate.
Hey, when you go into
a house of mirrors,
there's a bunch of reflections.
Does that mean you have a bunch
of reflections stuck in the mirror world?
No. All the reflections are me.
Whoa. How does that work?
I don't know. It's like...
I-I don't know!
Do you know how every part
of your body works?
Like, why do your blood cells
look like tiny inner tubes?
Because they're in a liquid,
and that's how they float?
They don't—
Wait, is that true?
Yeah. Wait, isn't it?
AD, what are you—
Oh, that's not
real grass, buddy.
So, how do we play the games?
What do they use
for money around here?
Points.
You gotta use 'em
to win 'em, friends.
Hey, it's you.
And you're getting kicked again?
Oh, it's not like that.
I operate this booth m'self.
Now people pay to kick me.
Please pay to kick me.
Oh.
Congratulations?
Let me give you young'uns
a couple of game cards to get you started.
Y'all get two points each.
Now go take a gander at the prize booth
in the center of the carnival.
Thanks, Toad.
Oh, please, call me Terrance.
Wait. Your name was Terrance
this whole time?
Nope.
Okay.
Hello, dearies.
Anything here that catches your eye?
Maybe one of these
unusual musical instruments?
I call it a buzzle-toot.
Tulip, what are you
still doing on the train?
You've given yourself
quite the makeover, kitten.
Oh, no, I-I...
I'm not Tulip.
I'm...
not Tulip.
C'est merveilleux!
A reflection!
I've never seen one of your kind
in the prime world.
How did you know that I—
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk.
Now, who is this
tomcat you have with you?
Hi. I'm Jesse.
Jesse, meet The Cat.
I got to know her when I was
still attached to Tulip.
She's a world-class con artist.
World-class entrepreneur, thank you.
Now let's cut the chitchat.
How many points do you have?
We each have two points.
Doesn't matter how many points
we have if the prizes are trash.
Well, I think I know what a handsome
young passenger like Jesse might need.
Want to exit?
Have to win.
Only those with 1,000 points
are allowed access,
and I must warn you:
you have a competitor.
And she looks like she plays to win.
So? If she wins, we'll just keep playing
and go through the exit later.
Oh, silly me.
I forgot to mention:
There can be only one
exit winner a month.
Who made that rule?
Wouldn't be a game without stakes,
but I'll tell you what.
If you two can win a combined
score of 1,000 points,
I'll give you both access.
Noblesse oblige and all that.
Attention, patrons of the Lucky Cat,
we have two new competitors for the door.
Let the Exit Games begin.
Better get a move on.
Why didn't we get
the same points?
The Exit Games are heating up.
If you'd like to place bets on the contenders,
please see the betting booth.
I don't think that was a real bow.
I think that was a sarcastic bow!
Where'd Alan Dracula go?
It's not real grass!
We have a winner!
Yes!
Gah! Water guy, I know
I just won that game.
Ah, hmm, uh, I don't know.
He must have actually won.
I have to give more points
to anyone with a number.
Passengers get preferential treatment
because they have a greater need to exit the car.
Personally, I'd run
my business differently.
Ooh, while we're on
the subject of commerce,
want to buy a Donut-Holer?
Ugh!
MT!
Guess not.
Came on a bit strongly, mate,
to be honest.
MT, slow down.
C'mon, where are you going?
I don't know.
I'm just... going.
What's wrong with this place?
Hey, it's okay.
It's still two to one in our favor.
That's not the point, Jesse.
The point is that everything
and everyone on this train
wants me to fail.
Hey, I don't want you to fail,
and I'm on the train.
And who cares about them?
Once my number gets to zero,
we're all leaving anyway.
What?
What what?
I-I don't—
I mean, I-I-I didn't think...
You want us to come with you?
You want me to come with you?
Yeah.
You're my friend.
I'm not gonna leave you here
with the flecs chasing after you.
Whoa.
See?
Even my number knows
you should come back with me.
It wouldn't have gone down
if it wasn't the right thing to do.
Well, if your number thinks so,
I guess I should.
Duh! So who cares if they give
passengers more tickets?
There's still two of us,
and we can still get that door.
If we could get Alan Dracula
to play, then there'd be...
I'm gonna smash that
crane game to the ground.
Ha ha!
Hm!
Spells.
Spells...?!
Ah, spells, spells, spells, spells!
We have a winning pair.
With a combined score of 1,084,
if you placed a bet in their favor, then—
I'm being told that no one bet
that they would win,
so all losers, please report
to the debtor's prison booth.
How do you like that?
So, you're just gonna leave
without your deer, then?
Ughhh, Alan Dracula!
Where is he? Where is he?
Uh, I don't know.
Is there some green
cotton candy around?
Ugh, what other dumb thing
would Alan Dracula think is grass?
Oh, look, Mummy!
That toy is moving.
I want him. I want him. I want him.
Ahh!
Ahh...
And our mystery competitor
has reached 1,000 points.
It's a race to the finish line!
Patrons who reported to the prison booth
may now return to the carnival.
The Lucky Cat is not obligated to return any valuables
already surrendered at the debtor's prison booth.
No, no, no, no, no!
We need both our cards
to win the exit.
Play the crane game!
Sorry, sorry!
Yeah!
Go!
Mummy, they took my precious little deer!
Please do be quiet, Arnold.
No!
Sorry, my little chartreuse.
A win is a win.
Well played, madame.
Thank you for patronizing The Lucky Cat.
Might not want to thank me just yet.
Let's wreck this place!
No!
You little Apex brats.
Sorry for the disguise, but...
I didn't think you'd give me
access to the door if you knew who I was.
You horrid little...
Wah, wah, wah.
Uh...
Huh?
So you won the door
just to let in a bunch of rabid kids?
Ugh, sorry.
Didn't realize you were, like,
super precious about this car.
D'ah! I'm not.
We're passengers.
We do what we have to to survive.
Plus, I wanted a corn dog.
Hey, kid. What's your number at?
Four?
Pff. We'll have to fix that back at my base.
Come on.
We're not just gonna
follow you wherever—
Look. I really don't care
one way or the other,
but you were trying
to win the door, so...
Ta-da! Door.
This car was cheating you.
I think she's okay.
She's letting us use the exit
when she doesn't really have to.
Fine.
Let's just get out of here.
This isn't over, Grace.
Try me, The Cat.
Ah!
One, take this corn dog.
Two, bring them
back to the base.