♪♪
[ Door clicking ]
[ Train rattling ]
[ Thud! ]
[ All cheering ]
Hmm,
isn't it beautiful?
It's okay.
Admire me.
How long have
you been on here?
What did you do?
A while. And what it took
to be the best.
[ Twinkle! ]
You got a name?
Nope.
You can call her MT.
Ugh.
I'm Jesse, and this
is Alan Dracula.
[ Snorts ]
[ Chews ]
Want some?
[ Chews ]Good?
Hmm, it's pretty good.
[ Swallows ]
I don't know why I said that.
It tastes like old pennies.
Then wheel it.
You don't like it?
Don't eat it.
Kick it to the wheels.
You do what you want.
[ Grunts ]
[ Thuds ]
Look at you.
I like what I see.
♪♪
[ Indistinct conversations
and laughter ]
♪♪
[ Crash! ]
Coooooool.
Yeah, we took over this car.
Now it belongs to the Apex.
Cool name, huh?
Yeah.
Huh. Kind of.
I got it from a book.
Grace, did you find
some more strays?
[ Warble! ]
My second in command, Simon,
I trust him with my life,
even if he was wearing
black socks and sandals
when I first met him.[ Laughs ]
Thanks for letting me
keep my cool factor
for 10 seconds there.
Whew, we caught you
just in time.
I thought I was doing
pretty good.
Yeah, look at you two.
With those numbers, you'll
be stuck here forever.
[ Both laugh ]
Ugh.
I'm sure you had the best
of intentions...
you, but I'm afraid
you've been leading Jesse
in the wrong direction.
This is what you want.
This is strength.
But when I was in that pod,
the conductor told me
to get my number down.
He was funny and gloomy.
The little white thing?
It's fake. It took over the
train from the real conductor.
We've been on this train
longer than you.
Neither of us got
intro videos from that liar.
He took over and
started brainwashing people.
And now for some reason,
this fake little robot
wants to get rid of all of us.
It wants to kick us humans
off our rightful train.
This was the conductor.
This is real.
I'm real, and because I have
the highest number,
it's my responsibility
to correct that robot's lies
because I care about people.
I care about you, Jesse.
Oh, I almost forgot why
I came here.
A new car dropped down
about two ahead.
I was hoping to take some scouts
to give it a look.
You know, it's been a while
since I've checked out
a freshly made car.
I'll take this one.
Jesse, will you be joining?
Excuse me? Hi.
I respect the whole vibe
you've got going on here,
but we don't...
Wait.
Where's Alan Dracula?What? The deer?
Probably taken
to be stabled.
Didn't think you'd want him
running off.
Stabled?
You took our friend
and locked him up?
You didn't think to check
with us or with him?
Hey, MT, they were probably
just trying to help.
Mistakes happen.
We're all human.
I appreciate that, Jesse.
You sit here
and find your friend.
You can talk to Simon
if there are any problems.
While she's doing that,
you'll come with me
so you can see what we do.
Is that okay?
Yeah, that's fine.
I'll make sure Alan Dracula
is safe.
We'll talk later, okay?
All right. Now let's get
you a harpoon pack.
Whaaaaaaat?
Cool.Whoa, slow down there.
You don't want to end up
like Lucy.
Aim first, okay?
♪♪
[ Gasps ] This is the
best day of my life.
I know.
I'm clipping you so I
can catch you if you fall,
but also don't fall
because I've never tested it.
♪♪
Aah!
Alan Dracula!
Do malls have crane games?
Check it out.
I'm all wobbly!
I'm not your prop, kid.
Yeah, you are, null.
Grace and Simon say
you're not even real.
Well, Grace and Simon
are about to lose
the shortest member
of their little club.
Psh. [ Laughs ]
♪♪
Huh? Huh-whaa!
You good?
Something I should know?
It's fine probably.
I just, um...
I-I don't know all of the rules.
I get it.
The train can be confusing
and lonely.
That chrome girl,
she's quite the character.
Oh, yeah, MT is great.Where'd you meet her?
She saw me putting sunglasses
on Alan Dracula
and wasn't a fan, but she stuck
with me when I needed it.
We rode a compass,
almost kicked a toad,
went to a carnival,
and, oh, yeah,
you were there
for that one.
She seems nice,
but she's a little bit
different from us, huh?
I mean, she doesn't even
have a number.
Yeah, well, she wouldn't.
She's not a passenger.
Exactly, she's a null.A what?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I forgot that
you don't know.
[ Chuckles ]
Null, it means nothing,
not even a zero.
I read it in a book.
Oh, uh, yeah.
Humans get numbers,
and nulls just tag along.
She's not bad.
She's just not like us,
and there's so many
more of them.
Hmm, I-I guess technically
she's not like us.
You've explored the train.
It's dangerous out there.
You almost jumped out of your
shoes when you saw these cubes.
It's not the cube.
It's the reflection.
MT's had some run-ins
with the cops.
I guess they would have
popped out for me by now
if they could have.
She'd be in trouble
though.
It sounds like she's got
a lot of problems
that you got pulled into.
We found a null.
Don't know if
it's dangerous.
Alan Dracula, where are you?
Alan Dra-- Whoa!
Huh?
Hold him still.
Come on.
What?
Hey, knock it off.
Whoa. Aah!Huh?
What is wrong with you?Aah!
Huh?[ Grunts ]
Ahhh.
Huh?
Yes!
Nice.
[ Growls ]
Aah!Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Simon is gonna have
some explaining to do.
Is it dangerous?
Doesn't seem like
he can touch us.
♪♪
[ Giggles ]
Does he have anything
besides these cubes?
Nuh-uh.
Not that I can find,
it's all junk.
[ Sighs ] Let's see.
Huh![ Shattering ]
Aah!
Huh?
Simon, do you have any idea
what is going on in your car?
Huh?
You're still here?
Your little toadies were trying
to saddle Alan Dracula.
He's shaking.
The deer?
What?
Hey, look at me
when I'm talking to you.
Who do you --I'm talkin' now.
I've got a number,
and you don't.
You two are only as good
as you are useful.
I thought we could at least
get something from the deer,
but now it's more hassle
than it's worth.
We're done with you.
Get out of here
before Jesse gets back.
You can't help him
like we can.
I'm afraid your first raid
didn't have any loot.
Next time will be better,
but that doesn't mean
it's a total waste.
Yeah!!
He doesn't seem
to like it.
Nulls can't actually
feel anything.
They're not real.
♪♪
Hmm.
[ Ding! Crackle! ]
♪♪
Empty handed
but high spirited?
Eh,
could have been worse.
Jesse was a natural.
Hey, where's MT?
[ Blows landing, MT straining ]
Hey!
Nngh!
[ MT straining ]
[ Gasps ]
Hey, let me go!
Jesse, don't listen to them!
M-MT?
I'm so sorry you two
had to see this.
I tried to take care of it
before you came back.
She broke Todd's foot.
What are you doing to her?
You don't need to worry
about it.
When you're part of the Apex,
the Apex takes
care of you.Stop it!
Tell me exactly what
you're doing to my friend.
Now.
She was trying
to trick you,
so we're gonna
wheel her.
I --
W-What?
What is wrong with you?!
Get your hands off her.
Jesse, think about
what you're doing.
Don't tell me what to do.
I'm not going to be a part
of anything like this
on or off the train.
I'm done with you.
And anyone else like you.
[ MT straining ]
Aah!
A-Aah!
[ Thud! ]
Ah!
Aaaah!
I'm sorry I left you.
[ Snorts ]
Aww.
Jesse, I tried to do it the easy
way, but you made it hard.
If you let the nulls take
advantage of you, they will.
You'll thank me
for this later.
[ Gasps ]
Aah!
How nice to see you again,
sliver.
Aah!
[ Both panting ]
[ Screeching ]
I don't know where
we can hide.
I got you.
We're getting out of here.
Huh?
Jesse, your number!
Whoa.
[ Whooshing ]
♪♪
We're going home.
We're free!
Ugh! Huh?
What?
Huh?
Jesse!
No, no, no, no.
Oh.
♪♪
[ Whirring ]Huh?
End of the line,
sliver.
♪♪