I can't believe
he took the exit.
He was weak.
He wasn't weak.
He was misled.
But he—
We just lost
another human, Simon.
Have some respect.
Jesse...
Huh?
No. Oh, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no.
Uh...
Huh?
Aaah!
Ooh.
Huh?
Ah! Ah...
Eh?
Ah!
Huh?
Wha!
Huh? Wha!
No!
Huh?
Ah!
Mace!
Ugh.
No.
No!
Ooh. Oh.
Oh.
Hey, buddy.
You okay?
That's right.
Back to the train.
Back to the train
like a good girl.
I saw a train go racing by
On exit day, on exit day
It gave a boy an exit
What got left on the train that day
On exit day, on exit day
A lonely little sliver girl
On exit day in the morning
Or afternoon, maybe.
Not a lot of clocks
on the train, are there?
[ Growls ]
Shut it, skin suit.
So...
...what's
the plan now?
Your boyfriend's gone,
little sliver girl.
I didn't see myself
going out this way.
How about you,
little sliver?
Was this the way you saw
your glorious escape going?
Eh, no matter.
My job is done.
You're as good
as sanded out here.
I'll see about that.
This was never gonna
end well for you.
You should have
followed mirror law
and been recycled.
Choose to become
a disgusting flec like you?
Coward.
What did you just say?
You're a coward!
When your prime died,
you chose to be a flec
because you were afraid
to let go of your identity.
It wasn't about keeping
my memories or identity.
It was about respecting
the balance our kind provides.
Ugh!
Why are you
like this?
Was your last prime
this much of a jerk,
or is this pure you?
Why can't I go forward?
It's...
It's—
It's the train!
Huh?
Ah!
Sliver girl, human boy,
and super deer!
Going from car to car,
learning lessons.
What an adventure.
You really fancied yourself
a regular passenger
out there,
didn't you?
I've been
exploring the train,
same as Tulip or Jesse.
Oh, sure.
I mean, that must be
why the train
is so keen
on getting you back,
so it can help you get
your shiny green number down,
or— Oh.
So sorry.
Forgot.
You don't have one.
You don't
know anything.
What did you
think would happen
if you were allowed
through the exit?
You'd just go out
into the world
with your metal skin
and your magic deer,
and what?
High school? Prom?
College? Job?
You and your prime
with parallel lives?
I would...
I-I'll figure it out.
Th— The train isn't gonna
let you exit.
The train can't
stop me from—
Did you ever wonder
why that car was there?
The mirrored car,
the chrome car,
whatever you want
to call it?
Your prime couldn't have
gotten out of the car
unless you switched.
No one's prime could have,
so did the train make the car
so you could get out?
You're trying
to freak me out.
It won't work.
Maybe the car was for you.
Why would—
To use you
to help Tulip learn.
Just another creation of
the train to help passengers.
No.
I'm a person.
I-I was making
my own choices.
Oh, choices,
and choices
lead to lessons.
And what were you
learning, exactly?
How to become what the boy
needed you to be?
It wasn't like that.
We were friends.
We are friends.
But they all make friends,
though, don't they?
Companions?
Stop it!
Stop laughing!
You might even say you became
his counterpart,
might say you became
kind of a...
reflection.
Ugh!
I hate you!
I don't— I don't care.
What? Did you think
you're free?
That—
That you escaped?
You're stuck
on the train now.
You're just in
another mirror.
No.
It's not like that.
Face it.
Being a reflection
is all there is for you.
I don't care what the train's
been doing or why.
I know who I am, and Jesse
didn't want to leave me.
We're friends,
and that's real,
and I'll get off the train
and find him!
Oh, yeah?
You and what number?
I'll get a number.
I'll...
Those pods.
The ones that drop off
new passengers.
I'll find one,
ride it back
to wherever it came from,
and I'll make this train
give me a number.
We're going,
Alan Dracula.
Alan Dracula,
come on!
Waaah!
Ah!
Wah!
What are
you doing?
I'm as good as dead,
and if my last act
is to bring you with me, sliver,
I can't imagine
a better way to go.
Well, I can!
Now we wait
for a pod.