Here's the plan,
Alan Dracula.
We're gonna sit here for however long it takes,
wait for one of those weird pod things to fly by,
and as soon as it does,
we hijack it for ourselves,
ride it back to
wherever it came from.
Passengers get a number somewhere
before waking up on the train,
and... I'm guessing
the pods will lead us there.
And then... I'll find
a way to get a number.
I'm serious.
Now that Jesse is gone...
Look.
You're all I've got.
I need you to be ready.
No turning into stuff
that'll slow us down,
like a snail or a broken car or...
You know, once I get my number,
i-it means I'm eventually
gonna leave the train,
and... I don't think
I can take you with me.
Even if I could, you wouldn't
be happy out there.
Getting off the train
is my journey.
I-It wouldn't be fair
to force you to leave.
This is your home.
You're not my pet.
You're my friend.
You know that, right?
Aw.
Which is my 16th
favorite kind of giraffe
you'll see on the train.
Necks are kinda weird, right?
Huh?
What's going on?
Please remain in your pod.
Ahhhhh!
Ahh!
Ahhh!
Ahhhh!
Please return to your pod.
C'mon, Alan Dracula.
Get comfortable.
Thank you for returning
to your pod.
Greetings, passenger.
If you're watching this, it means
we've run into an unforeseen problem,
but not to worry!
For every problem, there is a
documentary!
Ugh!
Gimme a break.
We're now en route
to the Tape Car.
Off, please.
This is where
all the magic happens.
And by magic, I mean
numerical algorithmic judgment.
Oh! Just saying it makes me
warm and fuzzy inside,
because very soon,
your pod's gonna get fixed,
and you'll be sent
back on your way.
Too bad you're asleep
and you'll never hear this.
Hmm. I suppose this documentary
is more for me than anyone else.
Maybe it's time I stopped.
Yes, do that!
Instead, I'm gonna guess
what Atticus is doing right now!
Ugh!
One, barking.
Two, rolling over.
Three, he's dead, a pile of dog bones
on the side of a long-forgotten road.
Four, he's only playing dead,
a pile of not bones on a not-forgotten road!
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la!
We're here!
What?
Don't get excited,
it doesn't look very special.
Fun fact: the Tape Car is the only car
where the universe is projected on the outside.
It's what's outside that counts.
Ah, the robot's
out of his mind.
What? Uh...
Uh...
Ah! Ahhhh!
Oof!
Ugh...
Alan Dracula!
Ugh.
You okay, Alan Dracula?
Eugh.
What is this place?
Shh!
Hey. Don't eat that.
Hmm?
Mom, this one!
That's a bearded dragon.
Do you need some help?
No, I can do it.
It was an accident!
Honey, I told you not to—
It was an accident.
What is this?
Huh?
They... don't care about me.
Hey, weirdo!
Come on, Alan.
Let's keep moving.
Ahh!
Alan, stay back!
Alan?
No! No, no, no!
Whoa! Oh!
Sorry!
Ahhhhh!
When all of this is over,
you and Jesse are
gonna laugh about this.
This'll be funny.
Whoa.
Ah, thanks!
I can do 8:30.
This proposal is ridiculous.
Yes!
Uff da!
I better get a smaller number than that.
Sorry. I need this more than you.
Mom, this one!
That's a bearded dragon.
Do you need some help?
No, I can do it.
It was an accident!
Honey, I told you not to—
C'mon! Hurry it up!
Huh?
No! I'm here!
Give me a number!
Ugh!
Listen to me!
You don't think I deserve
a number, do you?
Well, you gave
a number to some lady
who was sad
about her dead lizard!
How is that fair?!
What?
Do I need a sad-lizard story?
Is that it?
Ugh! Look at me!
I am a person!
I deserve a number!
Ugh!
Huh?
Hello!
I'd appreciate it if you'd stop
breaking everything.
Unless you want me to
start writing your obituary.