Do be careful.
I think you accidentally slipped
and broke a porter.
Many, many times in a row.
Hey, I know you.
You're the rare foil version
of my friend Tulip.
Aghhh!
I'm not Tulip.
I'm not foil.
I'm not reflection.
I'm not a sliver.
I'm not a null.
I'm not any of
the hundreds of names
that everyone wants
to give me.
I'm my own person who is
getting off this train,
and whatever gears
or reality-bending buttons
you've got to press,
you're gonna do it.
But why would I?
You're exactly where
you're supposed to be.
-No.
-No?
No.
Give me my exit.
You can't have an exit.
You don't have a number.
Ugh!
Give me a number then!
Numbers are for passengers.
How can I expect someone
to grow emotionally
without some
nice, juicy math?
Fine. Give me some trials,
whatever.
Take my memories.
Tape me.
I don't care!
Let's do it!
No, you'll stay
and keep helping.
You're so good at it.
I can show you.
Ah, let's see.
What was
your passenger's name?
Jesse.
His name is Jesse.
Oh, yes, thank you.
See? So helpful.
Here we go.
He got down to zero,
all sorted out
and off the— hmm?
He can't be at zero
but also in process.
So if he's being
processed...
Then he's back
on the train.
Field trip to
the passenger farm!
Alan Dracula!
Oh!
Hey, buddy.
Jesse!
Field trip to
the memory-watching machine!
Well, I don't get it.
We fixed him already.
Yet that greedy little
piglet is thirsty for more.
Oh, new release!
Gimme, gimme, gimme!
Let's take a peek.
Ahhh!
Ooh, a tape has never
started on the train before.
Remember,
you can't spell "escape"
without companionship.
Uh, companion-shape?
Companion-scape.
Com-scape-ionship.
Constipation.
Hey, come back!
That didn't
explain anything.
...of transformation.
Ah!
I didn't realize
he was so scared.
Ah!
Oh, look, you've got
costar billing now.
But you'll probably
be paid less
because Hollywood breeds
gender inequality.
You can't even
help yourself.
That's why passengers get on
this train in the first place!
Hey, don't push...
Ah!
Your friends are bad.
You know that, right?
Maybe.
Oh, train does it again.
Look how much he's grown.
I guess I changed, too.
I got you.
We're getting out of here.
This is my favorite part.
Please don't show me this.
Ah! Ah!
MT?
Where'd you go?
MT!
Jesse! Jesse!
Where have you been?
Nate. Ah!
I wasn't sure
I'd see you again.
I shouldn't have let
those guys hurt you.
I— I shouldn't have
hurt you.
I'm so sorry.
Ah, i-it's okay.
Wh-What about you?
Where did you go?
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
we don't need to hear it.
We just watched
the hi-def version.
And now I'm here,
and she's still trapped
on the train
with those flecs.
Do you think she's okay?
I don't know.
I mean, she's MT.
She can probably
take care of herself,
but I promised
we'd stay together.
So...
what are you gonna do?
I— I just need to sit here
and think for a bit.
Okay?
Okay.
Uh, I'll go get some food
or something.
Be right back.
I can't leave her there.
Uh.
Now will you wake him up?
Oh, heavens no.
Waking a passenger
is a whole process.
It involves robots and coding
and juice boxes and—
-Ugh!
-Wha!
-Ah!
-Ah, ah, ah!
Where am I?
MT!
Jesse, I thought
you were gone!
MT, I didn't think
I would find you so fast!
[ Both talking rapidly at once ]
AD!
Excuse me, young man.
This train is
for fixing problems,
not for hang time
with buds.
Oh, I have a problem.
My friend is trapped
on a train.
Whoo-hoo!
Number time!
Ah! Ah!
Okay, this is terrifying.
Ah! Hey, let go of me!Oh, stop it.
You'll hurt
my steward's feelings.
Ah! Ah!
Uh, is that
supposed to happen?
The train fixes problems,
but his problem is that he needs
to rescue his friend.
But his friend is a
denizen who can't get a number.
She can't leave.
So his problem is unfixable.
No, no, no, his problem
has to be fixed.
That's what we do.
We're the fixers.
We fix.
Oh, I have an idea.
Why doesn't she go with?
Good plan.
Oh, but she doesn't
have a number.
She has to get off, but she
can't get off without a number.
He's stuck in a loop.
The train can't process it.
There's no escape, sliver!
Ah!
Oh, leave me alone!
I won't go back!
I'm not taking you
anywhere.
I'm taking you out.
You killed Mace.
No more badges.
No more protocol.
But he can't leave with her.
That won't work, but I guess
he won't get off the train.
Number, number,
number, number, number.
Hey, you!
It's your lucky day.
You got a problem?
I got a solution.
He can't save her
if there's nothing to save.
Just help me sand her.
Problem solved!
Yeah,
that would solve things.
No!Wait, um, One-One,
I'm confused.
What's the purpose
of the train again?
Oh, it's to help passengers.
But wait. Your problem needs us
to let a denizen off.
Can't do that
without a number.
So I guess he can't
leave and...
-Aah!
Hey! Aah!
Ugh.
Jesse! Ah!
Agh! Agh! Agh!
Ugh! Ugh!
I only killed Mace because
he was trying to kill me.
And I'm finishing it
for him.
Ah! Agh!
Come on.
Ah, but he needs to get off
the train, too, but if she...
Ugh. Ugh.
Oh.
One-one, look!
I have a number.
So you can give me
an exit.
That's how it works,
right?
He can't leave his friend,
but she's a denizen.
Denizens don't have
numbers.
But you have a number,
so...
So we get our exit?
Hmm.
Yeah, sure, whatever.
Ah!
Huh?
We're leaving together,
for real this time.
Aaah!
Oh!
No! Ah! Ah!
You're done, sliver.
Whoa!
Ah! Ah!
Alan Dracula!
Aah! Aaaah!
Wow!
That was something, huh?
Well, looks like I gotta
get you back home.
I really broke the mold
with you, Alan Dracula.
I'm...
I-I'm off the train.
Yeah, you are.
Jesse, you better not
disappear again.
The chrome girl is real.
Yeah, yeah, get it
out of your system.
Hi. I-I'm Nate.
Uh, hi, Nate.
I'm...
Hmm. Dracula Two?
Mm.
I'm Lake.
Cool name.
Your brother's got
good taste.
Aah!
I wanted to be cool one time,
just once.
Nerd.